Wayne: Where do we begin?
My name is Wayne—
Trog: My name is Trog.
Baaulp: My name is Baaulp.
Log: My name is Log.
Gir: My name is Gir.
Wayne: —And this is the Where Do We Begin
podcast.
Your podcast, my podcast—
Log: Our podcast.
For everyone.
Baaulp: Anyone can make an episode of this
podcast, not just
us!
Wayne: We dump this shit in the Creative Commons,
I--we
haven’t monetized it yet, it’s up for
grabs.
It’s got potential!
Gir: It is… audible.
Log: This podcast is open source, so I’m
really expecting
one of you guys out there to add in online
play.
Eventually.
Alright?
Baaulp: Yeah, and there’s a—and there’s
a really nasty bug
where I sound super nasally, someone should,
uh, fix that.
Trog: And add wavedashing.
Wayne: Can we get widgets?
Can we get like, uh, like
Warframe drops—
Gir: No, that’s part of the past.
Trog: Nope.
Log: I swear I will install a bitcoin miner.
Trog: We should say this is, uh, the Where
Do We Begin
podcast, now with a new permanent home—well
not permanent, but a new home on
uh, what is—what is the URL, Baaulp?
Wayne: It’s called wayneradiotv.podbean.com,
and now I am
Baaulp.
Gir, chuckling: Thanks, Baaulp.
Trog: Alright.
Wayne: Yes.
Gir: Yes.
Trog: That’s part of the new change, is
that Baaulp is now…
new.
And sounds different.
Wayne: Baaulp, so where else can we find,
uh, Where Do We Begin and, our other podcast,
Do You Like Games?
Baaulp: Uh, we have an RSS feed now that you
can subscribe
to, and as of recording, we’re like, up
and running on Spotify.
I’m waiting on
Log to draw me a nice, uh, 1400x1400 square
pixel, uh, image that we can use ‘cause
apparently that’s a very strict requirement
for iTunes.
Wayne: Our listeners need those dimensions.
Trog: Yeah.
Log: Yeah, and I’ll get to that, but, today
I got inspired
to draw a picture of Akuma wearing a Nascar
jacket covered in Little Caeser’s
logos, so that’s what I’m working on right
now.
Baaulp: Okay.
Trog: Which is much more important.
Baaulp: Yeah, alright.
Trog: ‘Cause it’s relevant, as this—it’s—it’s
more relevant
than this podcast will be when you hear it
a month from now.
Wayne: Little Caeser’s is so much more important
to Log than
any of us and any of our needs.
Log: Yeah, if you’re a subscriber to Log’s
content, you
might even get the reference whenever this
comes out in 2019.
Baaulp: I had a—I-I had a disturbing amount
of Little
Caeser’s as a kid.
Wayne: I was about to say—yeah, Little Caeser’s,
I think
they’re like very close to death.
I think they’re on life support.
Gir: I’ve had them once this year, and that
was the
first time in eight years [laughing].
Wayne: When—When I moved to this town, I
noticed that, like,
five minutes from where I lived there was
a Little Caeser’s and I was like,
“Eugh, Little Caeser’s, I’m never going
to go there.”
[Bauulp laughs]
Wayne: And like a month ago I was like, “Y’know,
I don’t
have too much money, Little Caeser’s is
food, I think—I think it’s time.”
And I drove over there, this is after a year
living here, and I drove over
there and they’re just fucking gone.
And I was like, “Oh shit!
Did this
specific one close or did they just go out
of business?”
And I Googled it and
no, there’s like, a lot of closing downs
of Little Caeser’s.
Wayne: And I mean, it makes sense they—it’s
a bad model
for business, honestly.
Log: You know what’s the worst model for
business, though?
Wayne: What?
Log: Papa Murphy’s.
Baaulp: What the fuck is Papa Murphy’s?
Wayne: I don’t even know what—that’s—that
doesn’t exist in
my state.
That’s not a New England thing.
Gir: Papa Murphy’s is you—you go in there
and you’re like,
“I want this kind of pizza,” they make
it and they’re like, “Alright,
take it home and go put it in your oven.”
Trog: Yeah, it’s like a—a take ‘n bake.
Baaulp: Wow—they don’t even cook it for
you?
Log: [Crosstalk] They basically make microwave
piz—uh, well
not microwave, it’s like—they pretty much
make frozen pizzas for you, on
demand.
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] What?
Wayne: But it’s like a fresh oven pizza.
Trog: Yeah, it’s like a fresh—it’s not
frozen.
Log: It—It’s like, it’s like, fresh
Wayne: I feel like that’s not a bad idea,
but I’d never go
there, is the thing.
Log: So the thing is that it used to be the
super economical
option.
It used to be… that—it’s the Papa Murphy’s
price was a lot cheaper, and
that stopped being the case.
And so I see—
Wayne: Now they’re premium.
Log: —As far as I’m concerned, Papa Murphy’s
is just a
landmark to know that I’m really close to
the neighborhood my grandma lives at.
Baaulp: Wh-wha-what-what’re they charging
for your pizzas if
they’re not even cooking them?
Log: You can get a Little Caeser’s pizza
for as much as a
Papa Murphy’s uncooked pizza.
Baaulp: Oh my god.
Gir: What, you don’t like eating uncooked
pizza?
Wayne: But I bet a Papa Murphy’s one would
taste better.
Trog: Yeah.
It’s gonna be better than a Hot-N-Ready.
Log: I don’t know.
Baaulp: But you’d have to cook it yourself!
Log: It’s like what’s the point if you
have to cook it yourself.
Wayne: I think it’s genius on their part
from like, an
employment standpoint, because at that point
almost—there’s like almost no
liability on the employee’s side.
It’s like, “Oh you burnt your pizza?
[Laughing] Alright, buy another one.”
Gir: Why’d you fuck it up, idiot.
Wayne: Can’t do anything else.
Trog: Talking about pizzas has reminded me
uh… of a question
I wanted to ask you guys, and this is like
a super specific question, but I had
it happen to me recently.
Has there ever been an eating establishment
that you
used to enjoy and go often, and then they
got like, a new employee who f—sucks
at their job, and, like, it has made you not
want to go back there—Has that
ever happened to you?
Gir: Absolutely.
Trog: Because that happened to me recently.
Wayne: It’s definitely happened, but, uh,
it didn’t dissuade
me enough from going there—
Trog: So there’s a place near where I live
called Pie Five.
I don’t know, do they have those where you
guys are at?
Wayne and Baaulp: Nope.
Gir: No, that sounds like it’s probably
your area.
Trog: Pie Five is like a chain where they
do—It’s kind of
like the Subway of personal pizzas, you go
and you say, like, “I want a sausage
and a pepperoni pizza,” and they make it
in front of you and they put it in
this oven and then five minutes later your
pizza is done and you can eat it.
Uh, used to go there—
Baaulp: That sounds like, uh—that sounds
like Blaze pizza
that I see popping up here in Boston.
Gir: Yeah we got—we got Blaze here, too.
Trog: Yeah I’m sure that there are similar…
similar joints
in other locations.
Around here, there’s just one called Pie
Five.
But,
can’t go to the one near my house anymore
because they hired a dude who does
not know how to make pizza, and the last,
like, three times I’ve been there
he’s been the only person behind the counter,
and he has just made horrible
pizzas.
Trog: Like, I’ve never seen somebody, like,
put so much
cheese on a pizza before.
And you would think that that wouldn’t ruin
a pizza,
but there’s definitely a level of cheese
in which a pizza becomes inedible, and
he has found it out.
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: Nice.
Trog: And will only give me that much cheese.
Wayne: He’s surpassed the slop threshold.
Trog: Exactly.
Baaulp: How much cheese is this dude throwing
on the pizza?
Gir: A brick.
Trog: Like, so much.
Like a mountain of cheese, it’s
ridiculous.
[Log laughs]
Trog: And it’s—
Gir: He just throws a whole damn brick on
there.
Trog: —It’s sad because I used to like
it.
Wayne: That’s just how he likes it.
His boss just tells him,
“Alright man, make the best pizza.
Make the pizza you’d wanna eat.”
And he’s
just like, in his head, there’s only one
word, “Cheese.
Cheese.”
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: Aw, man.
Wayne: As he dumps the entire vat of cheese
onto your
fucking pie.
Trog: Here’s the thing—so it’s a double
whammy because number
one, he’s not very good at making pizzas.
Which, you know, I can maybe
look past, but also, he’s the kind of person
who like, every time I went in, he
like, feels the need to make small talk with
me.
Wayne: Oh, this is the same story.
Trog: He’s like, “Ah you play any video
games?”
And I’m
like, “Yes, sometimes, I guess.”
Wayne: “Play any video games, turbo?”
Trog: This is completely unprompted, also.
I’m not like, wearing
any video merchandise, he just asks me this
apropos of nothing.
Baaulp: He can smell the games on you.
Trog: Yeah, he can smell it.
And he was just like, “Oh,
you—you play Fortnite?”
And I’m just like, “No, I don’t.”—
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: I would’ve laughed.
Trog: It’s like—I don’t know.
It’s like every time it’s a
new awkward conversation and I suck at making
small talk already, so this… this
combined with the cheese mountain of pizza
that he makes for me every time—I’m
just like, I don’t even want to risk
walking in there and seeing him behind the
counter, like.
I will walk in and
then do a 180 and walk out if I see him.
Gir: Ah, it’s a shame.
Baaulp: I’ve never had that problem, but
most places here in
Boston are like a revolving door, y’know.
You go in like a month later and the
people are—
Gir: Someone completely different.
Baaulp: Different, yeah.
Log: Yeah, I absolutely do not recognize any
employees at
any fast food place I go to, even if I go
to them a lot.
The only person I
recognize is the lady that’s always at the
Starbucks counter at my work.
I
always—I know that lady, that’s all.
That’s the only person.
Wayne: The people that I recognize at like,
food
establishments is usually not fast food places,
because, like, they’re so fast
and loose with like, hiring people at like
a Taco Bell or a McDonald’s, but the
McDonald’s I go to, I think they’re breaking
a labor law.
I’m pretty sure
they’re hiring like, a thirteen year old.
Trog: Oh no.
Wayne: There’s this kid, he’s so small!
And his voice
is—he sounds like-like a little boy, and
it’s ridic—like—
Gir: Gotta make those V-Bucks, man!
Wayne, laughing: Maybe!
[Trog and Gir join in on the laughter]
Trog: [Unintelligible]—A job!
Wayne: I could just be being mean, and this
could be an ad—a
grown man who—with a child’s appearance,
but this kid is—
Baaulp: He could be a gnome.
[Gir laughs]
Log: Do you want to buy a McGun?
Wayne: I’m so tempted to just say, “Hey
man, how old are
you?
I think they’re like, tricking you.
I don’t think you’re s’posed to work
here.”
[Gir laughs]
Trog: They’re paying him in Bionicles.
Baaulp: Hey, it could be the other way around.
I knew kids
who were definitely, y’know, fudging the
numbers on their age so they could get
jobs.
Wayne: At like, family owned businesses, though?
Like—
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: That’s the thing—
Gir: That’s more likely.
Baaulp: No, I mean, like—I mean like Dunkin’
Donuts and-and
stuff.
Wayne: You have to show your fucking birth
certificate!
Like—
Trog, laughing: You don’t have to show your
birth
certificate—
Wayne: Are they—yes you do!
You have to show, like proof
of-like—like maybe not your birth certificate,
but I absolutely—like when I
went—when I worked at Taco Bell and I worked
at an agriculture store, I had to
show like, legal proof of my identity, which
would include my birth—
Gir: Yeah, this is a—you said this is a
family owned place,
right?
Wayne: No, Baaulp was saying Dunkin’ Donuts.
Gir: Ohh.
Trog: I mean, are fake IDs hard to get nowadays?
I never
owned one.
Wayne: I mean, I don’t know.
I think you can just order fake
IDs online, but if you’re gonna go through
the bullshit to order a fake ID
online to work at Dunkin’ Donuts—
Trog: To work at McDonald’s—
Wayne: Yeah.
Trog: Honestly, Wayne, with the stories that
you tell… about
where you are…
Your place of living sounds like an anarchist
zone, I think
everybody just breaks laws over there.
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Wayne: Maybe.
Trog: Secretly living in an anarchist commune.
Wayne: I don’t know.
Have I talked about the-the heroin
couple on a podcast yet?
Baaulp: No.
Trog: I don’t know.
Baaulp: What?
Log, laughing: Probably not.
Gir: I don’t think you’ve told us, ever.
Wayne: There’s a couple that comes into
my store, both of
them will go into the women’s bathroom which
is just like a one-one person
bathroom, for like, ten minutes, and like,
I can’t say for sure what they’re
doing in there.
Who knows, maybe they’re just—maybe they’re
just really into
each other, y’know, maybe they’re shooting
up, I don’t know, I can’t say
for sure.
But one thing I do know is that after ten
minutes of a
bathroom session, they’ll go out and play
in the refill litter bin like it’s a
sandbox.
[Baaulp, Log, and Trog laugh]
Wayne: I don’t live in a bad-I don’t—I
mean, I guess
I don’t work—I don’t work in a bad spot
in Connecticut, but it, uh—
Gir: It’s not a good one, either.
Wayne: It’s weird.
Wayne: It’s—no it’s just, I don’t
know.
It-it might just be
the mass exposure to the people of a suburban
area, I think that’s a constant.
I think this is everywhere.
Baaulp: It’s definitely here in the northeast,
‘cause your
stories line up with the stories my friend
uh, tells me about working in a
liquor store.
Trog: Man, northeast sounds crazy, I don’t
know—I live in a
suburban area and I don’t see anything nuts.
Gir: I see that kinda shit where I work.
Wayne: Well you live in like, Vegas, that’s
even—
Gir: Yeah, but—
Trog: Crazy shit happens there, you just go
like, a couple
streets over and you can see like, people
running around in Sonic costumes and
shit.
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: My favorite is a guy getting his—he
was like trying to
shoplift and they’re like, “Hey put that
back,” and he sets it down like, “Oh,
don’t worry I’ll be back tomorrow.”
Wayne: Well pretty soon, Trog, you can get
that experience,
too, in theaters.
Trog: Are we going to talk about that?
Is that our segue to
move off of, uh—
Wayne: I mean it could be.
Trog: It could be.
We could be the twenty thousandth
podcast, probably, to talk about the mistake
that is the Sonic live action
movie that’s going to come out here in 2019.
Wayne: You wanna, you wanna talk about sickness,
instead…
Baaulp: Sure.
Trog: No?
Wayne: Well, I’m sick.
Gir: Let’s get down with the sickness, man.
Baaulp: Let’s talk about death and disease
as
a refreshing break from every podcast talking
about Sonic.
Log: I can tell you about… something positive.
Wayne: Do I sound sick?
Trog: No, you sound normal.
Wayne: Alright, good.
Chat… you’re not chat—
Trog, laughing: Chat—
Wayne: This isn’t my stream, listeners—
Trog: “This isn’t my”—this is recorded—
Baaulp: Hey, chat—
Wayne: Listeners, if you hear this stream
and you knew I was
sick—It’s not a stream!
Okay, my brain is sick.
[Trog laughs]
Gir: Holy shit, dude.
Wayne: I’m done with this one.
Log: It can be, whenever we make this podcast
open
source.
Wayne: I’m done with this one.
Trog: Yeah, this could be a live stream.
Wayne: Let’s talk about….
Whatever you guys wanted, and not
what I wanted.
Trog: Sonic?
Log: Bro, I can talk about something positive
instead of
something horrible and terrifying.
Trog: Alright, let’s go with that, I like
that better.
Log: You guys are familiar with a white elephant
gift
exchange, right?
Trog: Yep.
Gir: Uh, no.
Wayne: Mhmm.
I’ve done that uh, just once, but yes.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: You’ll have to explain it for Gir.
Log: A white elephant gift exchange is one
where you and a
group of other people all put presents in
a pile, they’re not aimed at anyone,
they don’t, like, they don’t have a specific
target, and you all just take
turns picking a random present from the pile—
Gir: Ohhh.
Log: —Opening it, and you, you get that.
Or you steal a
present from somebody else who has already
opened a present.
Gir: I did that once, I took ‘em all.
Trog: Yep.
Log: Yeah, you just go around in a circle
and you do that.
I
think I’m the first person ever to have
won a white elephant gift
exchange.
Trog: Uh-huh.
Baaulp: Oh shit.
Wayne: I won mine as well, I think, but I’ll—you
go—you
finish.
Log: Could you objectively say that you won
it though, because
I definitely did.
Wayne: Well I wanna hear yours and then I’ll
compare it.
Trog: Did you destroy all the other presents
so you’re the
only one left with a present?
Log: Okay, let me just tell you.
Uh, so the-the gift price
limit was $20, okay?
Wayne: You got a 20 dollar bill!
[Trog laughs]
Log: I was the last person to open the gift.
So, everybody
goes around, there’s one thing left, I pick
it up and open it—it’s a $25 gift
card.
[Gir laughs]
Trog and Wayne: Ohhhhh!
Trog: Somebody broke the rules!
Wayne: Okay!
Gir: Nice.
[Wayne laughs]
Log: One of the people from work just fucking
ignored the
rules and bought a $25 gift card!
Trog: Was that person fired immediately?
[Gir laughs]
Log: We did kill him.
Trog, laughing: Oh, well, okay, that’s a
little bit more
extreme.
Gir: Aw, I thought it was positive, what the
fuck?
Wayne: Well I mean, your coworker’s dead,
but twenty-five
bucks.
Log: Yeah, I didn’t get hurt.
Wayne: That’s… pretty good.
Trog: What was it a gift card to?
Log: Amazon.
Trog: Ah hell yeah, that’s the best kind.
Wayne: I gotta say, that-that man as an entry
to that game,
that was so lazy.
Oh, like, you’re s’posed to do something
interesting, like-like
if you had a $25 Amazon gift card, like, and
other people saw that, everyone
would just take it.
Like, that’s the whole point of the white
elephant, right?
‘Cause
they can just steal it.
Log: Here’s the thing, I fuckin’ won because
I was the last
person to open a present, and then the person
that was first—the person that’s
first always gets a chance to steal something
at the end because otherwise it’s
unfair for them—but the first person was
the guy who brought the gift card, so
he couldn’t steal it.
Trog: Ahhh.
Baaulp: Ohhhh.
Gir: Ah, nice.
Trog: Well he could have.
Log: That wasn’t what our rules are, though.
So he wasn’t
allowed to take it.
Wayne: And-and that’s the thing, I feel
like white elephant
is more interesting when you pick a gift that
has like, a—a versatile a, like,
attraction to it.
Like, some people will want it, some people
won’t.
Log: I bought the gift that I brought yesterday,
and I
bought it because it—I looked at the shelf
and it said, “Yogibo Grippibo” on
it.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: Uh, what was it?
Wayne: I know what a Yogibo is, that’s like
a bean bag,
isn’t it?
Log: It’s… it was a thing that was—
Wayne: Is it like a grip toy?
Log: It was something that you wrapped around
your neck and
it held up tablets in front of your face.
Trog: What?
Wayne: Ohhhh—
Trog: Okay.
Gir: Ohh, that thing.
Trog: That’s pretty interesting.
Wayne: You bought that?
Log: Yeah.
I saw the name “Grippibo” on it and then
I bought
it.
Wayne: That’s—oh man.
That’s great.
That merchandising team
must have a lot of fun.
Trog: So I feel like we’re getting our-our
Christmas
nomenclature possibly mixed up, because, to
me, that’s like—the whole like,
“everybody grabbing a gift,” that’s
just called a gift exchange, and a white
elephant gift is specifically like—I’ve
heard white elephant referred to as,
“specifically getting like, shitty gifts
for each other.”
Wayne: Nah.
Trog: Like—like gag gifts.
Log: Nobody knows anything anymore.
They just pick a name
and go with it.
Like, I’ve heard a bunch of different names
for it, and I think
I’ve heard at least one racist name for
it, that I’m not gonna say.
Baaulp and Trog: Oh.
Trog: Well, let’s not talk about that one.
Wayne: My family’s tradition is called,
“The Gnome Blender,”
in which no one buys any gifts.
Gir: And we blend a gnome.
Trog: Nice.
Wayne: Oh no I don’t—I don’t know why
they call it that.
Log: Yeah, positivity’s over.
We can get into your-your
horrible, shitty, bad vibe space, now.
Trog: I don’t feel like there’s much to
discuss that
probably…
Wayne: Should I just cough into the mic?
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: No.
No, no, no, no.
[Log laughs]
Baaulp: Yeah, that would be—that would be
great—
Trog: No, no, no, no.
Wayne: I don’t want to get germs all over
my pop filter.
Trog: I think we should talk about the elephant
in the room,
and then we should leave it, which is—
Wayne: Is the white elephant.
Trog: The white elephant in the room—
Gir: We already talked about the white elephant.
Wayne, laughing: Have you guys heard of this
white elephant
gift exchange thing?
[Trog, Log, and Baaulp join in on the laughter]
Trog: The new Sonic looks fucked up and I
hate it.
That’s
it.
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: Alright, movin’ on.
Trog: I just want that to be an available
opinion of mine.
Wayne: I mean we still haven’t seen its
true face.
Gir: Its true form.
Trog: It doesn’t matter!
Wayne: We’ve seen his legs.
Baaulp: Its face doesn’t matter because
they ended up
deciding to make a 3D humanoid Sonic, and
there’s no possible way to
make that attractive in any way, like, its-it
can only be ugly.
Gir: Yeah.
Trog: Yes.
I mean, okay, so at the time of this recording
there
are two pieces of media for this.
There is a silhouette poster, and then
there’s like, a bigger poster that’s like,
his fuckin’ dick POV—
Gir: Dick cam.
Trog: —over the Golden Gate Bridge.
Wayne: That shit—the calves fuck me up.
Those calves are not
good to look at.
Trog: No, so like, he has like, hairy human
legs…
I don’t
know.
It-it’s messed up.
Wayne: It’s weird.
Baaulp: Nintendo knew what they were doing
because when they
moved from 2D to 3D they kept Mario the way
he looked, but like, they fleshed
things out.
Sonic did not get that kind of treatment,
so when he moved from 2D
to 3D he looked like shit.
Like, let’s be real, he looks like shit
in 3D already
for the video games.
Here, they’re doing like a… weird… humanoid
Sonic with like, realistic fur…
This can only be a disaster.
Log: I think that Sonic looks fine normally—
Gir: Yeah.
Log: —I, for some reason after I saw the
movie poster, I
just forgot that there’s countless sources
of 3D Sonics for them to draw from
and they instead made a realistic version.
Trog: [Crosstalk] Yeah.
Gir: [Crosstalk] Yeah.
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: That’s my major issue with it.
Trog: They made a new one, that’s the problem.
Wayne: Hey, do you think they’re gonna,
like, obviously the
community is going to voice the fact—and
they already have—that this is awful
and disgusting—
Log, laughing: Sega already voiced the fact
that this
is awful and disgusting!
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: Yeah.
That’s the biggest thing!
Is they admitted
beforehand like, “Yeah we made a change
to Sonic and Sega didn’t like it, but I
think it’s important that we keep this change.”
Wayne: But what I’m thinking—Do you think
they’re gonna pull
a Jared Leto and say like, “Oh no, that
was just a tribute.
The real Sonic
is coming soon.”
Baaulp, laughing: “This is a Sonic tribute!”
Trog: “This is a Sonic tribute, we made
him look like
a hairy man!”
[Log laughs]
Gir: Their-their reasoning is like, “Oh
it would look weird if a cartoon character
is next to real people.”
Like-like that looks better?
Trog: Yeah, as if that hasn’t been in countless
beloved
films.
Log, slow and drawn out: “Hey, gotta go
fast!”
Wayne: However, you can take that into consideration
and
make it not look bad—like case in point,
like I was talking earlier, I think
the idea, Gala—Guardians of the Galaxy is
very successful and I think they’re
trying to aim for like a Rocket Raccoon-like
character.
I mean, Rocket Raccoon
just looks like a rock—like, he looks like
a raccoon.
Trog: He looks like a raccoon.
Wayne: He just looks like a raccoon, but he
does have like,
anthropomorphic characteristics.
Trog: So, so here’s-here’s where that
falls apart, is that
Rocket Raccoon is a raccoon.
Sonic the Hedgehog bears no
resemblance to a hedgehog whatsoever and is
a hedgehog in name only.
Wayne: Now would you enjoy the Sonic movie
if it was
shot with real people, with Jim Carrey Eggman
and Sonic did not look
like Sonic, he looked like a Rocket Raccoon
style, just like a real hedgehog.
Small, that size, and blue.
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] Yeah.
Yeah.
Trog: So they’re trying to do half-and-half
is the thing.
They’re trying to do like, a fucked up—
Wayne: And that’s why you get an amalgamation
like—
Trog: Yeah, it’s not good—
Wayne, laughing: You get a monstrosity.
Trog: The other thing I wanna bring up about
those two
pieces of-of Sonic posters that are out is
that, unless I’m mistaken, the Sonic
movie takes place on like, Mobius, right?
Like, that-that’s been said.
Why is the post—
Wayne: Wait really?
Trog: Yeah!
That part was like, released a long time ago
whenever they announced that it’s like,
Jim Carrey and shit.
Wayne: Isn’t he on the Golden Gate Bridge?
Trog: Yeah no, that’s what I was gonna say!
Why is he on the
Golden Gate Bridge if it takes place on Mobius?
Wayne: I don’t know, maybe they’re pulling
some stupid shit
and it says like, “Oh, this is…
Mobius, the alternate universe… of Earth.”
Trog: Maybe.
Gir: “The alternate version of Earth.”
Wayne: “Where Sonic is real and nothing
else is different.”
[Trog and Wayne laugh]
Log: Do you think that Jaleel White is going
to bring out
his Sonic voice against hecklers?
Trog: Yeah—
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: —for sure, you know all of those Jaleel
White live
performances, I guess?
Wayne, laughing: Hecklers.
No, they heckle him in
public.
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: “Fuck you!
Why did you let Sonic Underground get
cancelled!”
Log: I can’t do a Sonic voice, but somebody
should try and
just put something together that’s just
a Jaleel White voice saying, “Hey, shut
the fuck up!”
Gir, impersonating Jaleel White: “Hey, you
guys need to shut
the fuck up!”
Wayne: You can’t do it—No one can do it.
Trog: Nah, that’s not Jaleel White, you’re—that’s
like Sonic
Adventure’s Sonic.
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: That-that-that’s modern, yeah.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: You gotta stretch it out like the
way Jared Leto
would say it.
Wayne, pinching his nose: You gotta—You
gotta pinch your
nose!—Ah I can’t even do it.
Trog: Jaleel White Sonic is like really nasally.
It’s
a-it’s a very nasally…Sonic.
Wayne: It’s very nasally.
Trog: And it’s because it’s uh, because
Sonic is actually—
Gir: Jaleel White.
Trog: —Family Matters.
They’re the same.
Gir, in a nasally voice: “You guys need
to shut the fuck
up!”
Trog: That’s the secret canon they don’t
want you to know.
Wayne: Where’s Carl in the Sonic universe?
Trog: He’s Eggman.
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] Oh shit.
Gir: [Crosstalk] Ahhhh, okay.
Wayne: I believe that.
Trog: Welp, that’s all the—that’s-there’s
your Sonic Minute.
Gir: There you go.
Trog, laughing: Our weekly segment where we
talk about
Sonic.
Log: Yep, yep, yep.
Trog: Tune in-tune in next week.
Gir: In three months from now when we finally
make the next episode.
Wayne: Hey, so did you know that you can buy
a live chicken
on Craig’s List for fifteen dollars?
Baaulp: Yeah, I’m not surprised.
Why?
Wayne: For some reason, I always—in my head—thought
that
they’d be more expensive, but I guess it
makes sense considering you can get
some chicken breasts for like, a couple bucks.
Log and Trog: Yeah.
Log: You can buy a dead one for… pretty
cheap.
Gir; Yeah you can go to like a feed store
and get chicks.
Trog: [Crosstalk] I’m pretty sure—
Wayne: [Crosstalk] Yeah.
Trog: —like, the sum of the chicken’s
parts is probably
worth more than the chicken itself.
Wayne: Shouldn’t life be more valuable?
Baaulp: Listen, I know we might have some
vegans and
vegetarians listening, I’m sorry, but like,
come on.
Chickens… chickens are the
food animal and they’re born of food.
They come from eggs.
Gir: They are born of an egg!
Wayne: I think we—yeah, that doesn’t mean
you eat snakes!
Unless you’re snake eater.
Baaulp: We do in China.
Wayne: [Crosstalk] I guess so.
Gir: [Crosstalk] Every animal is up-up for
grabs, dude.
Wayne: Every animal comes of food!
What the fuck are
you talking about?
Gir: That’s—I didn’t say that, you said
that.
Wayne: Cows are not born from eggs, but you
eat the cows
which they come from!
No, I’m not targeting you, I’m targeting
Baaulp.
Baaulp: If I eat a-eat a jellyfish, that doesn’t
come from
food.
Trog: I’m sure you could eat a jellyfish.
Gir: What the fuck is this conversation?
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: This is a weird podcast now.
Log: You should eat the core of the apple.
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: How much would you buy a chicken for?
How much would
you pay?
Log: Uhhh…
I don’t want to buy one of those.
Wayne: What’s the value?
Gir: A dollar.
Wayne: I’d like a chicken.
Log: Sometimes I’ve had dreams… or just
like, just like
fantasies of having just a pet duck that roams
the house and is like a dog that
walks on two feet and quacks.
Wayne: Speaking of dreams, do any of you guys
have like
recurring stressful themes in your dreams?
Trog: [Crosstalk] Yes.
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] Nah…
Every dream is different.
Wayne: I consistently—Not-I mean not every
time,
every dream is different, but like, it comes
back every once in a while.
For me, and this is one that just happened,
just before—I-I am sick today,
listeners, and just before this podcast I
was taking a sickness nap.
And during
that nap I kept falling back asleep into a
dream in which I had forgotten that
I had a pet opossum in a box also filled with
two hundred mice, and I
was—the entire dream’s plot was me trying
to figure out a way to put the whole
box in a bag before all of the mice could
run out, and every time I failed I
would just quick-load with a picture on my
phone, and that was the dream.
Trog: [Crosstalk] Nice.
Wayne: And it was-it was—No, it was terrifying.
Trog: Oh, okay.
Bad, then.
Wayne: There were mice everywhere.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: Well, that is unfortunate.
Baaulp: That’s very specific.
Gir: The most stressful reoccurring dream
that I have is
like, and you guys are gonna rail me for this
one but, I’m trying to go
fishing and somebody keeps bugging me.
Trog, laughing: That-that’s the most stressful
dream
you’ve ever had?
Oh my god.
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne, laughing: You are a simple man.
[Gir laughs]
Log: Man you live the b-you live the best
life, don’t you?
Gir: You know how fuckin’ obnox it—obnoxious
it is?
Trog: Gir lives a stress-free life the most—the-the
like the
literal most stressful thing your brain can
come up with is just, “Aw man, I’m
fishing and this guy won’t leave me alone.”
Wayne: So what’s he doing?
Is he just like on the co-on the
shore just going like, “Hey!
Hey man!”
Gir: It’s always something different.
Wayne: Alright, yeah one time he’s just
going like, “Hey,
what’re you-what’re you fishing for?”
And then other times he’s throwing r-he’s
throwing rocks at me.
Gir: It’s not just a dude or something,
half the time
it’s something insane.
Wayne: It’s an eldritch force—
Gir: Sometimes it’s—someone is talking
to me, or like I
don’t have a lure that I need so I get lost
in a store trying to find a lure I
want or—
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: —all the water dries up.
Trog: All the water dr—Alright, that one’s
pretty wild.
Baaulp, laughing: So you’re not even really—it’s
not even
like a mischievous force, these are things
you would have to do if you
went fishing anyways, like buying lures and
renting a boat.
Gir: Yeah, what if I went fishing and the
ocean was
gone.
[Log laughs]
Wayne: If I was Gir, having Gir’s dreams,
and I-and I dreamt
that I was wet in someone else’s car that
I didn’t know, and I was trying to
fish, I would probably be pretty upset about
it, too.
Trog: Yeah.
Nightmare scenario right there.
Gir: I got crumbs on my ass.
Trog: My stressful reoccurring dream is because
I was in
marching band for four years in high school.
Well, for reference, I haven’t
been in high school for… like, eight years
or something?
But, I still have
reoccurring nightmares where I’m like, on
the football field and like, I don’t
know what the music is because I haven’t
been in marching band for eight years
and I’m like running into people and fucking
the show up.
[Baaulp and Wayne laugh]
Trog: It’s not good.
That’s my reoccurring stressful dream.
Log: Uhh…
I don’t know.
I don’t want to get too focused on
dreams-talk, because I don’t know how appealing
that is to yonder folk.
Trog: Anything we say is gold.
Wayne: See, that honestly—so that is a legit—that’s
a thing
that goes around a lot, is like, I hear that
just different podcasts were like
if dreams come up people are immediately like,
“Alright, we have to stop.”
And
I understand the whole like, you don’t want
to be sitting there for ten minutes
explaining a very convoluted dream, but if
you can talk about it quickly there’s
no problem with it.
But if you want to move on, if you have another
great topic
for me, hit me with it.
Slap me with me it.
Gir: Slap me around a little.
Baaulp: Here’s what I think.
Fuck ‘em.
Fuck ‘em, we’ll break
all the rules.
Fuck you, uh, what’re-what’re-what’re
some—I don’t listen to
podcasts, what’re some people who have good
podcasts?
Log: Uhh…
Let’s see… we got Scissors and my Friends.
Baaulp: Scissors and my Friends, fuck you.
Trog: No.
No, no.
We can’t go down this hole.
Wayne: Masters of Music, hosted by Zarknon
the
Embarrassed.
Baaulp: Fuck—fuck him.
[Trog laughs]
Baaulp: We’ll-we’ll talk about dreams
all we want.
I got
dreams.
I want ice cream.
Trog: I got a topic that most of us here can
talk about
and is relevant as of this recording.
The new Smash Brothers came out and most
of us here have been playing it.
Baaulp: Not me.
Trog: Everybody except for Baaulp.
[Baaulp sighs]
Trog: And we’re definitely some kind of
video game podcast,
so I’d say we’re somewhat equipped to
talk about that game.
Wayne: I think everyone in this call except
for… uh, Gir,
shares the same opinion on it.
Trog: Probably.
Gir: It’s fun and I enjoy it.
Wayne: It is somewhat fun, but the problems
that it has are
extremely hindering to my full enjoyment of
the game.
Trog and Log: Yeah.
Log: They keep fucking around with online
play and really
they should just stick with something that
works.
It’s Bandai Namco, they have
a lot of experience making games that are
just all about snappy online play.
They have Tekken, they have Soul Caliber,
they sort of have Dragon Ball
FighterZ, technically.
Arc System Works developed that but Bandai
Namco—
Wayne: They definitely did the netcode, though.
Not Bamco.
Log: Bandai Namco owns all those IPs and whatever,
but
anyways, they have experience and they just
fuck it up every time.
And they
really…
make me… wanna start punching.
Trog: Yeah.
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: They make me wanna smash a bro.
Wayne: Well yeah, then start uh, go play Smash.
Trog: That really what it comes down to, because
my history
in Smash is I liked the first two, and I liked
Brawl for a while, but then it
got boring.
I didn’t really get into 4 because I didn’t
like how it played, and
I feel like this one is—I’m not crazy,
I know that they’re never going to make
another Melee, it’s not gonna happen.
So this one, seems to be like a
lot of fun considering the fact that it’s
not another Melee, but the online is so
bad, that all you can do is play the single
player or play in person.
Wayne: And that is the ultimate sin.
It—yeah… the online—I-lots
of people are doing it, and I don’t understand
how.
Even-even with the ethernet
adapter I hear it’s still pretty bad.
Log: Yeah, we should take this time to talk
shit about
Bandai Namco ‘cause they’re doing everybody
a disservice.
[Trog laughs]
Log: So, Smash Brothers online sucks, Tekken
World Tour
prize money sucks, let’s talk about that
one, too.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: How much was that again, Log?
Log: So the winner of the Tekken World Tour,
and just to
preface this for people who don’t know about
Tekken and fighting game
tournaments and stuff, to qualify for the
Tekken World Tour you have to be in
the, like, top 20 ranks and their tour points
rankings, and to do that you have
to win tournaments all over the world, they’re
not segregated by region or
anything.
If you’re from Korea, you need to fly over
every continent in the
entire planet and win tournaments everywhere
to qualify for the tournament.
And
so, people did it, a Korean guy won, he won
seven thousand five hundred dollars.
Trog: For the record, that’s nothing.
Log: To further elaborate on that, so yes,
seven thousand
five hundred dollars is nothing for something
that culminated over the course
of a year.
His sponsorship immediately collapsed afterwards
because they
couldn’t make any money.
Wayne: Yeah, the guy who won got dropped.
Log: The sponsored players of that sponsor
we’re just the
guy that won in the tour tournament and the
guy that won Evo, so.
Trog: The two biggest possible tournaments.
Log: The two biggest winners of 2018 and then
the
sponsor caved in.
Trog: Yeah.
Log: Just another comparison, in 2006, the
winner of the
United States rock paper scissors tournament
got what, fifty thousand dollars?
Trog: Fifty thousand dollars.
Wayne: That was like, that was also 2006—
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: —so, accounting for inflation, that
was a lot more
than the Tekken World Tour winner.
Trog: Bamco is… it’s-they’re sending
some mixed messages
because on one hand they are still doing the
Tekken World Tour.
They’re
still like, supporting the game in the way
that they are creating these events
and avenues where people can compete, but,
the problem is, is that they’re
putting so little money into it outside of
hosting the events that nobody can
afford to play Tekken professionally.
All of the biggest Tekken players pretty
much have gotten dropped from their sponsors
at this point.
Wayne: It’s ridiculous.
The game is pretty popular for a
fighting game—
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: —It’s-it’s no Street Fighter
V, it’s pretty popular,
but they’re not putting the money into it
that they need—like, how much money
are Street Fighter V’s winners making?
Trog: Hundreds of thousands.
Log: Yeah, hundred thousands.
Wayne: It—That’s fucking unacceptable.
Log: Yeah.
Wayne: Someone needs to kick their ass.
Log: Tekken 7 I think is the best selling
fighting game of
this generation, and it’s owned by the people
that own the video game
production rights to One Piece and Dragon
Ball Z, so…
They c-they can afford to boost it, they just
don’t.
Wayne: Kick Bandai Namco’s collective ass
and make the money
fall out.
Log: Let’s see what they show us in January,
they’re
probably going to start the new Tekken World
Tour by then.
Trog: Is Tekken more popular than…
‘Cause in my head I was
thinking Tekken is probably third place in
popularity behind Dragon Ball
FighterZ and Street Fighter V.
Wayne: Is FighterZ the most popular right
now?
Trog: In my head it is?
But I don’t actually know if that’s
true or not.
Log: When it comes to tournament scenes yeah,
those have bigger
numbers, but in terms of like, just people
buying the game and playing it,
Tekken I think has the highest reports on
that, and it’s consistently played in
all platforms, y’know.
I think it’s a very popular game, and yeah,
they’re
just-they’re just being stingy little goblins
over there.
Trog: So go write to your local representative
and demand
that Bamcai—Bam-Bamgo… make more money.
Gir: Bamguy Bamgo.
Log: Let’s exterminate the Bamcai, let’s-let’s
capture them
and put them in-put them in video game prison.
Baaulp: The thing is this, like, what-what
is their
structure like?
Aren’t there outside tournaments?
Like is Evo a part of the
Tekken World Tour?
Like how’s that-how’s this work?
Log: No, it’s not.
I don’t want to get into it.
Trog: We could talk an entire episode about
this if we
wanted to, but—
Wayne: Yes, we’re not a fighting game podcast,
and those who
don’t really know about it aren’t going
to enjoy it.
Trog: No.
But this is the Fighting Game Minute—
Wayne, laughing: The Fighting Game Minute—
Trog: —our weekly segment where we talk
about fighting
games, and it comes right after the Sonic
Minute.
Log: The Fighting Game Minute, it takes a
lot longer
than that.
Wayne: We should make that reoccurring and
make it an actual
minute where we have to talk about as much
fighting game content as
possible, and we can achieve this goal with
four people talking at once.
Log: Yeah.
Gir: I’m down for that.
Baaulp: We haven’t recorded in three months,
is there any,
like, life thing—
Wayne: So much—
Baaulp: —we wanna talk about first, or?
Wayne: I could tell a story about something
that happened at
work.
Trog: Go for it.
Wayne: So, sometimes customers are old ladies,
and need help
getting bags out to their car, and that’s
perfectly fine.
It’s like a forty-pound
bag of dog food, they’re not going to be
able to lift that over their heads,
out of the cart, and in to the car.
Uh, I get called up, and the lady that I
have to carry out for is like, a very-a very
old, feeble woman, she’s very
sweet, very nice, uh, she’s very thankful.
Trog: But very feeble.
Wayne: But very feeble.
I could flick her and she would
perish.
And we go outside and I’m like, I grab the
cart and I’m like, “Alright,
I’mma, uh, I’ll push the cart you lead
the way.”
And she’s like, “Okay.”
And
she does that.
She leads me to her car, she’s parked—Our
parking lot is on an
incline, and the incline goes further uh,
downwards away from our store.
So,
we’re like at the top of a very, very tiny
hill.
It’s not much of an incline,
but it’s enough that like, if something
was left to free roll, it would
go down that ramp.
Wayne: And uh, so, I’m pushing the cart,
and she’s in the
very first spot, the handicap spot at the
top of the parking lot.
I go to the
other side of her car, away from the-the building,
and uh, she says, “Hold on,
let me open up the backseat,” and she does,
and uh, and I’m like, “Alright,”
And I’m-I go to like pick up the bag and
I’m like, “Alright, ma’am you’re gonna
need to hold the cart, just so it doesn’t
roll away.
‘Cause without the bag in
it, it’s not gonna-it’s not gonna sit
still.”
Wayne: And she’s like, “Okay.”
So I pick up the bag, and I
see her going for it and then at-at which
point I take my eyes off that
scenario and I-I go—I go for the three seconds
it would take to put the bag in
the car and shut the door, and then I hear
her say from behind me, “Where did
it go?”
[Trog laughs]
Gir: Oh no.
Wayne: And I turn around and the cart is like,
fifteen feet
away from us, rolling away, and just as I
look it slams into the driver seat
door of an-of an SUV—
[Trog groans]
Wayne: With this like, nasty looking white
trash lady
smoking a cigarette with an open window, just
smokin’ the cigarette, “DOOK,”
hears the thud of the—hears the thud of
the carriage, and just gives us like,
the most—the-the biggest stink eye, and
doesn’t say anything and just keeps—and
just takes another drag off her cigarette
and is just staring at us, the old
lady’s just staring there, and I’m just
like, “Uh… bye.”
And I just left.
[Trog laughs and Gir sighs]
Wayne: And I-like, I don’t know what happened
after that, it
wasn’t my fault!
It was entirely the customer’s fault, and
we are not
responsible for cart damages in the parking
lot.
But it was very funny.
Trog: Blamin’ an old lady, I see how it
is.
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: It was very, very, funny.
Wayne: Alright, so time for questions?
Trog: It’s time for questions, I’d like
to start—
Wayne: Q’s and A’s.
Trog: —this round of Q and A with a disclaimer
that
it has been so long since we recorded any
episode of the podcast, I can’t
remember what questions we already answered.
So, if we retread our steps, I
apologize, but I’m not going back and listening
to the rest of the podcast to
figure out what we answered.
Wayne: I always listen to the podcast after
Baaulp is done
with them, so I’m-I’m pretty sure I’ll
remember if we’ve already done one.
Trog: Okay.
Here’s a question we definitely haven’t
answered before, and I’m very excited to
answer it.
Got a question from KingMusicManz
who asks, well, it’s more like a task, but,
they say, “Describe a method à la
Hitman of how you would assassinate another
member of the group.”
Gir: Hm.
Log: Uhh…
Wayne: Baaulp would be the easiest to kill.
Baaulp: What?
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: You would not-you would not taste-he
would not taste
poison in his food.
Log: Yeah, you could poison Baaulp at basically
any given
minute of the day.
Baaulp: I know what everything is supposed
to taste like,
fuck you.
Wayne: Actually, y’know, you do.
The dinner-the dinner is
such a high focus in your brain that maybe
you will recognize the slightest
change.
Gir: Baaulp is like when you need to medicate
a dog.
Log: You could also easily get into his room
from outside.
Wayne: Alright, I could kill Gir real easy.
Gir: No.
Wayne: When he goes fishing I hide under the
lake in a scuba
suit—
Trog: Alright—
Wayne: —grab his fishing line—
Trog: I think I have an idea to make this
a little more
organized, so I’m gonna-I’m gonna change
this question a little bit, I’m gonna
ask, “If you were the target in a Hitman
level, where would you want it to take
place?”
Wayne: That’s a completely different question!
Baaulp: That’s a different question—
Trog: No, no, no, but that’s the-that’s
the start.
So
everybody’s gonna say where they want to
take place, and then we can
answer—then somebody else can answer how
they would kill you.
Wayne: I feel like that’s overcomplicating
it.
Gir: I want to sit in a room with five people
staring at me
at all times.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: No, no.
You got to pick something that’s like a
place
where you would be, that you would like-like
to be.
Gir: My room with five people staring at me—
Trog: No—
Gir: —at all times.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: This is not the spirit of the question.
You’re gonna
make this poor viewer—listener cry.
Wayne: Well you added in this new term!
This is your
fault!
Trog: I’m trying to help facilitate discussion
here.
Wayne: It was already good!
It was great!
Let’s go back to
the old one.
Trog: It wasn’t good, everybody just said,
“I’m gonna poison
Baaulp,” and that was it!
[Wayne and Gir laugh]
Wayne: Log, how would you kill me?
Log: Uhh, let’s see.
I’d probably come up with an exploding
dog—
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Gir: You’d come up with it.
Baaulp: He wouldn’t be able to resist.
Log: If I’m-if I’m Hitman they just have
the tech for me, I
don’t even have to come up with it.
I’d just have an exploding dog, and then
it
just goes up to you and… you don’t even
have to come to it.
It’s-I don’t-I
don’t even have to do the job.
It does it for me.
Wayne: I could tell.
I’ve seen a lot of dogs.
Log: Yeah, well, this is a new kind.
Wayne: It might be—I mean dogs are pretty
fast, I might not
be able to get away, but at that point why
don’t you just shoot me with a
Nikita missile from Metal Gear Solid.
[Trog laughs]
Log: Because I need to make it look like an
accident.
Trog, laughing: What?
How is an exploding dog an accident?
Wayne, laughing: Yeah!
Oh man this—oh no, Wayne accidentally
blew up during his training, aw.
Trog: This dog accidentally exploded!
Wayne: Shouldn’t have used that explosive
dog clicker!
Log: Aw dang, don’t you h—just hate it
whenever the dog just
has like, that collar that gives it a little
bit of a jump whenever it goes
past the invisible fence?
Who-Who’d’ve thought that if it goes five
hundred
miles past its invisible fence it just explodes!
Gir, laughing: You’ve gone too far.
Wayne, laughing: Alright, the dog’s gone
too far, the kill
protocol must be engaged.
Trog, laughing: We gotta-we gotta destroy
it.
[Wayne laughs harder]
Trog: I’m like imagining like, like a plastic
dog that’s
like, it can’t articulate in any way so
it’s just got like, chair wheels on the
bottom of his feet and is just like, slowly
rolling towards Wayne—
[Wayne and Gir laugh]
Trog: —playing like a barking clip out of
a speaker box
that’s built into its face.
Log: Tell you what, I’ll get the exploding
dog, it’ll be
plastic, I’ll leave it on the table just
in a place that you’ll be, and then
you’ll get a question mark over your head
and go to it, and that’s when I
detonate it.
Wayne: See, now I wanna imagine this scenario
but instead of
you doing it-it’s Agent 47, “Hello, I
need my dog trained, please.”
And
it’s just this like, plastic dog with wheels
on it.
[Wayne and Trog laugh]
Wayne: Aw man, they need to make more levels.
I mean, I
still have half a game to play through, but.
Fuck.
Trog: It’s true.
Wayne: Alright, so we gotta-I gotta hear-I
gotta hear
everyone’s answer.
How would-how would Baaulp kill me?
Baaulp: How would I kill you?
Trog: Are we all killing Wayne?
Or all we all killing
somebody else?
Gir: Yeah, what the fuck?
This ain’t no—
Wayne: Actually, yeah, here.
I’ve already done mine, and Log’s
done his, Baaulp you do one, Trog you do one.
Baaulp: How would you kill me beyond just
poisoning me,
which would work for anyone else?
Trog: I got a way.
So, I know that Baaulp takes public
transit, I would Agent 47 one of the drivers
of like, one of the subway cars,
and I would-I would drive the subway and I’d
press like, ‘detach car’ button
that he’s in—
Wayne, laughing: They total have—
Trog, laughing: —and then I would, I would
send him down
like, the wrong way into a brick wall and
he would cartoonishly run into it and
explode.
Gir: Along with all those civilian casualties.
Baaulp: Yeah, and I’m also in the subway
car alone
and no one else gets on.
Trog: I didn’t—Nobody said I had to get
a good score!
Wayne: You are not making use of all the buttons
that are
theoretically on the subway.
I would hit ‘turbo maximum’—
Gir: That’s not a button.
Wayne: —which is on every Boston subway
car.
Trog: But how are you going to get out of
it?
Wayne: Um, teleportation that I have—
Trog: No—
Gir: Nobody said he had to.
Trog: Agent 47 cannot teleport.
Wayne: Yes he can!
Trog: No he can’t!
Gir: You can’t turn on noclip.
Wayne, impersonating Agent 47: It’s time
to teleport.
[Trog laughs]
[Wayne makes a teleporting sound]
Gir, also impersonating Agent 47: Right.
Teleport,
Hitman.
Log: You’re really overcomplicating this.
I would just hit
the subway’s ‘jump’ button.
[Wayne laughs]
Log, laughing: And it would hit the-it would
hit the ceiling
and Baaulp would get crushed!
Wayne: Alright, welcome, welcome to the Boston
subway
training session.
Uh, first rule.
There’s a jump button.
DON’T PRESS IT.
[Trog laughs]
Wayne, laughing: YOU WILL KILL EVERYONE.
[Baaulp and Trog laugh]
Gir: What, this one?
[Gir makes an explosion sound]
Log: We here at Dahir Insaat think that implementing—
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Gir: Oh no.
Log: —this jump button onto the Boston subway
system will
let you have two subways going in tandem!
Trog: Oh god.
Log: Simply have one jump over the other.
Wayne: Supreme Dahir Insaat training facilities
will make
sure that drivers will always use button in
correct fashion.
Gir: Multitrack jumping.
Wayne: Baaulp, I would just wait until you’re
doing one of
your Let’s Plays inside a box, walk into
your room with a sledgehammer, and
just…
get you.
You wouldn’t see it coming.
Trog: How are you gonna get past his mom,
though?
Wayne: Oh fuck.
Actually, yeah, Baaulp’s mom would never
let me walk in his house with a sledgehammer.
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: And Baaulp’s mom is like, awake all
night, too.
Like,
we-we could talk to Baaulp so late in the
night and his mom will still be
up.
Gir: Y’know, I could very easily kill everyone
except Baaulp,
because all I would have to do is have a gun
and say, “Hey look!
Look how much
food Baaulp is eating!”
And you’ll turn around to look and I’ll
just shoot you.
It’s that simple.
Trog: I’m not that dumb.
Log: So you’d have to bring Baaulp, too.
Trog: I won’t fall for it now that you’ve
told me.
Gir: “Hey, look how much food Trevor’s
eating!”
And then I
shoot you.
Log: You’re indoctrinating Baaulp as your
Agent 48, here.
Wayne: You can just change it, turn on Baaulp’s
TV and just say,
“Oh my god, 13th century cooking!”
And then—
Gir: Oh no, I would say, “Hey—Oh my god,
Baaulp, look how
much food’s not being eaten!”
Trog: I would just roll an explosive television
into his
room that’s constantly playing tiny food
videos and How It’s Made clips.
[Gir and Log laugh]
Wayne, laughing: Yeah, you-you also add a
uh, a head sized
compartment at the bottom of the TV and it
says, “Put your head in here, extra
quality!”
And it’s a guillotine.
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Trog: And then just throw coins all around
his room.
[Gir laughs]
Wayne, laughing: To distract him
Trog, laughing: To distract him.
Wayne: Baaulp, Baaulp, Baaulp.
Okay, you are in your room
right now.
If you heard a coin hit the floor and land
behind you, would you
stand up and go get it?
Baaulp: I’m pretty slow, probably not.
[Log and Wayne laugh]
Log, still laughing: What, is your mom gonna
get it first?
Wayne, still laughing: Like-like you wouldn’t
be able to
reach it?
Baaulp: Eh…
Gir: His pathing is bad.
Wayne: What kind of slow?
Like you’re not fast enough
to get it?
Baaulp: When things fall around me, I don’t
really react.
[Log and Wayne laugh]
Baaulp: I’ve had like, chairs fall… next
to my head… and
stuff….
Trog: What?
How?
What?
[Log and Wayne laugh]
Wayne, laughing hard: How did a chair fall
next to your
head?
Were you lying down?
Baaulp: …A little.
[A moment of silence]
[Everyone bursts into laughter]
Gir, laughing: A little?
You can’t just lie down a
little!
Log: I think that’s-I think that’s called
sitting.
Baaulp: One time I was at the bus stop, and
the bus was
rolling up, but for some reason they were
going really fast and then
they like, slammed on the brakes kinda hard,
and as I was getting on the bus
the guy was like, “Hey!
Next time don’t stand so close!
The mirror almost hit
your head!”
And I didn’t even notice.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: ItsAGundamu asks, “If you could put
any character in Smash
Bros. Ultimate, who would it be?”
Gir: Ah, Goku.
Trog: I picked this one out because I got
an answer that is—and
we were talking about it, and I think this
is entirely possible.
And it is Sora
from Kingdom Hearts.
Baaulp: Sure.
Wayne: I would love Alucard.
Trog: Alucard would be pretty sick.
Gir: Alucard’s not gonna happen.
Wayne: I don’t even play Castlevania and
I would love
Alucard.
Baaulp: I want…
Goku.
Gir: Yes, there’s two for Goku.
Baaulp: ‘Cause everyone wants it, but like,
it’s possible.
It’s actually possible.
If they-if they’re willing to go as far
as to put a
Persona character into the game—like Dragon
Ball FighterZ is on the Switch, like
that’s even a closer connection.
Wayne: Someone I follow on Tumblr pitched
such an amazing
idea for a character to be added, and I can’t
remember what it was.
Gir: Oh, It was choir kids.
Trog, laughing: Yeah.
Wayne: I mean that’d be pretty cool, I don’t
know how they’d
do that, but—
Gir: No, it wouldn’t.
It would be so fucking dumb.
Trog: Um, I’m gonna say Sora or Killer Mike.
[Log and Wayne laugh]
Gir: Either one’s just as likely.
Trog: Yeah.
Log: Killer Mike and El-P will just be a echo
fighters for
Ice Climbers.
[Gir and Trog laugh]
Wayne: Oh, that’d be so good.
Log: Y’know, hold on, rewind the tapes because
I wanna take
the ech-the word echo fighter out of my mouth
and like, lay it down on the
counter and hit it with a knife.
Trog: See, they, they—
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: What?
Trog: --tricked you into calling them echo
fighters, now.
They got everybody.
Log: I was trying to use the game’s vernacular
but
really—echo fighter’s a dumb shit phrase.
It’s a clone.
Trog: It is.
Log: Every fighting game has called it clones
since the
beginning of time.
Why’s Smash Brothers gotta come up with
new funny words for
everything.
It’s like, “echo fighters,” and “jivvies,”—
Baaulp: Mama mia—
Log: —and “jimmies,” and “stevens,”
and “guessies,” and
“friendlies,” and—
Gir: Who cares?
Log: —“funny,”—
Wayne: And “whim-whams”—
Log: “Funny farms,” and “sillies.”
Baaulp: “Flim-flam.”
Trog: This isn’t funny but—
Wayne: Then why are y—Why-why bother.
Gir: Ehm, stop talking already!
Wayne: Fuck!
Trog: The explanation that I heard for calling
them echo
fighters and not clones is that like, clones
are like, a story thing in this
one?
Like, you’re fighting clones, like—
Gir: Oh, yeahhh.
Trog: —you’re fighting clones of things.
I’m not saying that
is a good reason for why they called it that—
Gir: It’s a fair reason.
Trog: I believe that was their reasoning,
was that they
didn’t want to confuse people.
I guess.
Gir: I think that’s fair.
Log: Alright, well—
Trog: Again, not-not saying it’s a good
reason, I’m
just saying that is the reason.
Log: I don’t know how much I-I wanna take
it.
I don’t th-I
don’t know how much I want to accept that.
We’ll leave it like that.
Wayne: I would love to see Banjo-Kazooie.
Trog: Yeah, of course.
That’s… y’know.
Wayne: And that one’s not even impossible.
Trog: Everybody-every—I want to see Banjo-Kazooie
in anything,
so badly.
Wayne, laughing: Yeah.
That one could happen, I think.
Trog: It definitely could.
Wayne: There’s a-there’s a potential.
Log: Tell ‘ya what I want and I’ve always
been saying it,
Travis Touchdown, man.
Trog: That would be a good one.
Wayne: Oh!
That’s one, I think that one will happen.
Trog: That one very well could.
Wayne: Season one is gonna fall around the
time of the
release date, right?
It’s next year.
Log: I dunno.
No More Heroes, a series that started on the
Wii, always came out on the Nintendo consoles,
Travis Strikes Again is coming
out soon, they’ve already included Bayonetta,
who’s like, a sexy character who
swears and makes blood everywhere, so—
Wayne: She doesn’t swear in Smash!
Trog: She doesn’t swear in Smash, but—
Gir: “Fuck you, Pikachu!”
Log: Yeah but she swears in Bayonetta, she
does swears and
she does-she does things that are not appropriate
for children to see, like uh—
Trog: Become naked—
Gir: Show a breast—
Log: Like doing combos.
[Trog laughs]
Log: Children can’t see those.
Wayne: Do you think they would maintain Travis’
jerking off
charge-up?
Baaulp: They’d have to.
Wayne: That’s so iconic.
Log: I think they could obscure it and it
would be safe.
Wayne: I-no, I think it looks worse if they
obscure
it, if—
Trog: Yeah, then it-then it looks like he’s
actually doing
it—
Wayne, laughing: If you see that from his
back and you can’t
see the saber anymore—
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne, impersonating the Smash Announcer:
Travis Touchdown
used his neutral B to jack off!
[Log laughs]
Log: They could do anything with that, it’ll
work.
Gir: Travis Touchdick.
Log: He just has to shake the sword anywhere
so, they could
do it.
Wayne: When he does his side B he says, “Fuck
head.”
Log: Yeah—
[Gir snorts]
Log: That’s a requirement, though so, Smash
Brothers is
about to not be for kids, I’m sorry to say.
Wayne: Now it’s for me.
Log: Yeah.
Gir: Well it’s got guns and grenades in
it, so.
Log: Isn’t it weird that they let Bayonetta
have guns but
never gave Snake his gun?
Wayne: Yeah, what the fuck.
Trog: Isn’t it weird how Mario’s in the
game?
Wayne: I mean Bayonetta’s are magic guns.
Gir: He’s about that CQC.
Wayne: Bayonetta’s are magic guns, which
you could say like,
“Oh, it’s magic guns, it wouldn’t kill
you like a real gun.”
But the whole
point of Bayonetta’s guns is that they are
much more effective than a
real gun.
Trog: They kill demons and angels.
Wayne: Yeah.
Trog: Crazy.
Moving on, we got a question from DoctorElsewhere,
who asks, “What’s your dream house?”
Wayne: Upside down, I can’t jump.
Gir: Oh man, I’m not allowed to answer this
one.
Trog: You’re not allowed to answer that?
Baaulp: Gir has to answer first now, now that
he’s said
that.
Trog: What-what’s up with your fucked up
house that you
can’t answer this question?
Gir: You guys’re just
gonna call me a fuckin’… simple man.
Baaulp: I just-I just wanna know.
You made it tantalizing.
Gir: I wanna house, middle of nowhere, in
the woods by a lake,
and that’s it.
Baaulp: Why do you feel like we would laugh
at you for that?
You can fish, that’s what you like.
Gir: That’s exactly it, is I just want a
house with no
neighbors, I’m by myself, out in the woods,
fishin’ every day.
Wayne: I want my house to be big, I think
it needs a nice,
clean, sheen coat of blue paint, and it needs
a bear.
Baaulp, laughing: A bear?
Oh fuck.
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: At the door, guarding.
Baaulp: Who would you live with?
Wayne and Gir: The bear.
[Gir and Trog laugh]
Wayne: The bear’s friendly, he sings!
Trog: And the moon sings to you.
Wayne: Also the moon-the moon has a face,
here.
Gir: You can see a face on the moon from my
house!
Baaulp: There were a lot of characters you
didn’t name any like,
of them, except for the bear.
Wayne: The little mouse.
Little mouse.
I don’t know I don’t
remember that much—
Baaulp, laughing: Little mouse.
Yeah.
Trog: Sure hope you were born between the
years of like,
1993 and 1997 to get these references.
Wayne: People know what the Bear in the Big
Blue House is!
Trog: Do they?
Baaulp: Yeah, I think they do.
Baaulp: Enough people do.
Gir: Oh, that’s what you were talking about.
Trog: See?
Gir didn’t even know what you were talkin’
about.
Baaulp: Gir, I gotta question for you and
your dream home.
Who’s gonna, if it’s a lake, who’s gonna
repopulate with fish?
You’re gonna go
ham on that every day.
Gir: It’s not like, a lake in the middle
of—I don’t mean literally
the middle of fucking nowhere, I mean low-low
population.
Trog: Now here’s the thing, though, if you’re
living in the
middle of nowhere, the Internet is gonna suck.
Gir: Yeah, I can live with that.
Trog: How are you gonna play Fortnite?
Wayne: There—I can’t remember what country
it is in Europe,
but there’s like a European country, I remember
reading like, the-the woman who
has the fastest Internet in the world lives
in the middle of nowhere.
Gir: That’s Sweden.
Wayne: Yes.
Gir: That’s some sw-old Swedish lady has
the world’s fastest
Internet.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: My dreamhouse would be… an efficient
house, in that I
don’t need like, a mansion.
I actually would rather have my house probably
only
have like, four rooms in it max, and like
maybe a couple living areas.
I would
like a space to put a bunch of instruments,
‘cause that’d be fun.
Wayne: I just want a studio.
Trog: Yeah.
Well see, I think a studio would be better
suited to-to not in your house, right?
Baaulp: That’s where you would go not in
your home.
Where would you come home to?
Wayne: I’m going to repurpose my-my wish
points that you’re
giving me with this question and put them
towards a studio.
Baaulp, laughing: Yeah, okay.
Trog: So instead of having a house that has
a studio in it,
you’re wishing for a studio that you just
can happen to live in.
Wayne: Uhhh…
I don’t know about that.
Gir: What you need is a nice big basement.
Wayne: But you need more than that for a studio.
Gir: No.
Trog: Yeah, like lights and a camera.
Wayne: It needs to be more than one room.
Gir: Uh, My family once house sat for someone
who had a
fuckin’ like million, two million dollar
home, and their basement was like, as
tall as my ceiling is.
It was like.
A few hundred square feet, or a few
thousand square feet in that basement.
Trog: On the topic of basements, to me, as
somebody who
lives in the south, where like, you literally
can’t build basements here
because the ground is too hard—
Gir: Same.
Trog: —Basements were such like a mystical
thing for me as a
kid that I was like, “God, I just want a
basement so bad, it just seems cool
to have a-a house beneath your house.”
Gir: Yeah, same.
Wayne: The basement is a special place.
Gir: You get old enough to be like, “Oh,
that’s the part of
the house where all the bugs live.”
Trog: And it’s smelly.
Wayne: That’s where I don’t go.
Baaulp: There might be radon in there.
Wayne: In the house I grew up in, we had a
uh, unfinished
basement, and then we finished it, and it
became like—It had two rooms, there
was the personal gym, and then to the side
was the TV room, and that was like,
where we had our 80 inch TV.
It would become belovedly known as the Space
TV in
this friend group.
Gir: The Big 'Creen.
Wayne: And I had-I had a lot of good memories
playing PS3
games down there.
It was a special place.
Gir: Nice.
Wayne: Not all basements are dingy.
Sometimes they’re nice.
Trog: One thing that I’m weird about when
it comes to
houses, ‘cause I’m actually uh, looking
to buy a house here in maybe like, a
couple years or so, is that I really don’t
want a two story house, but for some
reason I would be okay with a house with a
basement, which is essentially two
stories but it’s just like, everything is
moved down one.
Baaulp: Yeah, what?
Wayne: I mean, is it a visual reason?
Do you not like
the-like, the visual aspect of a two-story
house?
Trog: I don’t like the idea of stairs.
I don’t like the idea
of me like, having to go up and down stairs
to do things.
Baaulp: But you would need stairs for a basement.
Wayne: I feel that in most houses with a basement,
the
basement is a room that you don’t have to
go to on every day
Baaulp: Right.
Wayne: If you have two stories, your bedroom
is probably up
there.
Trog: Right.
Baaulp: Trog’s dream home is a one-story
home with a
basement that you descend via rope ladder.
Wayne, laughing: Yeah, make it harder.
Trog, laughing: Yeah, exactly.
I don’t want stairs.
Gir: No, he’s got an elevator in his own
home.
Trog: Or an escalator.
Baaulp: You have to get in a bucket and lower
yourself down.
Trog: Yeah, exactly.
Wayne: This is gonna like, like double up
on this question
but—so I don’t really have a big answer
for this right now because honestly
right now I’m not picky, I’d love-I’d
just love a house.
Honestly.
Baaulp: But what is your dream home?
Wayne: Even so, I know, that’s just like-that’s
just how I am.
I don’t like—
Baaulp: You can’t think of anything?
Wayne: I don’t think too…
large in terms of those sorts of
things.
Log: I wanna live on a spaceship.
Gir: Ah, shit.
I change my mind I’m with Log.
Wayne: I feel like if I had a lotta money
and could get a
house, in this case I’d just get a house
and I’d sit on that money.
And the
money would be spent on stupid shit, like
putting an image I thought was funny
on a billboard.
[Baaulp and Trog laugh]
Wayne: What I was gonna change this question
into was, when
you were a kid, did you have any like, house
features that you thought like,
“Oh man, that would be in my dream house.”
because like, I don’t have
that anymore, but—
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: When I was a kid, I thought a spiral
staircase was
the ultimate sign of decadence.
Trog: Spiral staircases are pretty sick.
Wayne: They seem dangerous.
Gir: You know what I would—I’ve always
wanted?
I’ve always
wanted a secret room.
Like you have to go into your closet and you
have to open
a little hatch.
Trog: Yeah, no I was literally-that was gonna
be my answer.
I still want one.
This is no joke.
Whenever you’re a kid and your
parents are watching the TV, you don’t get
to choose what’s on the TV.
I would
watch television with my mother who would,
as most white women do, watch HGTV,
the Home and Garden Network.
They literally had a show devoted to, “Here
are
houses with six secret rooms in them.”
And ever since I saw that as a kid, it
has been in my head that like, I want a secret
room in my house.
I want some
kind of crazy contraption, I wanna have to
pull the book out of the bookshelf,
I wanna like, Scooby-Do where—like, rotating
wall.
Wayne: What would you put in it?
Baaulp: Yeah, what would you-what would your
room be for?
Trog: It doesn’t matter, like that’s the
thing.
It doesn’t
matter what’s in it, it just matters that
it is a secret.
Baaulp: Just fill it with watermelons.
Wayne: Just put your Street Fighter cartoon
animation cel in
there and nothing else.
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: That’d be so good!
Trog: Exactly.
Like, you just open it and it’s just that.
Wayne: Like you invite somebody to your house,
“Hey man, I’m
gonna show you something that no one’s ever
seen before.”
Trog: This is my fucking secret room.
Get ready.
Wayne: And you-you play-you play the piano
password, the
door opens and it’s just an empty room with
the cel of the animation frame.
Gir: How I would have it is it’s a room
designed for any
future children I have to find, and then scare
the shit out of them.
Trog, laughing: Will you just fill it with
like, cartoon
skeletons or what?
Gir: I’m gonna fill it with like, really
scary shit, paint
like “GET OUT” on the walls or something
with something that looks like it
would’ve been blood.
Baaulp, laughing: Like a dungeon?
Wayne: That’s going to go wrong.
Gir: I want it to—oh no.
Trog: Nah, it’ll be fine.
Gir: It’ll be fine.
Trog: The police will never find it, it’s
a secret room.
Wayne: Just-just make it a room dedicated
to how much you
love your son.
Gir: It’s gonna be like there was a ghost
in there, not like
someone was murdered.
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: This is my secret son-love room, I
can’t-I can’t show
you this.
Baaulp: Ohh, that sounds wrong.
Trog: Make it a room devoted to how much you
love your son,
but it’s not pictures of your son, it’s
like, some other kid.
[Wayne laughs hard as Log, Trog and Baaulp
join in]
Wayne: Okay that-that is the ultimate-that
is like the
ultimate mind fuck for your future child it’s
like, this—okay, now is it the
same name or a different name?
Trog: Different name, like it’s a-it’s
a completely
different kid.
Wayne: Oh man.
Baaulp: “Who’s Tanner?”
Wayne: “I love my son, Jimmy.”
And it’s just like a stock
blonde kid, like—
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: Ah man, that is so good.
Trog: Drive your kid crazy.
Log: The first time that they see the room
it’s got all the
stuff dedicated to their new son.
The second time that they go to it, you’ve
removed all the pictures and stuff and you’ve
just placed the new son there.
Trog, laughing: There’s just a new kid there.
There’s a kid
there growing in a tube.
[Log, Baaulp, and Wayne laugh]
Wayne, still laughing: Oh my god.
Trog: I’m growing my new son.
Wayne: Even if-even if it was just a prop
of
that—Even if it was just a prop of like,
a test tube baby, and like, it had
like bubbles in it and shit, oh man.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: Make a real mindfuck for your kid,
have pictures of
a different kid and have different—pictures
of a different father.
[Everyone laughs]
Trog: Yeah, make him think that he went to
fucking Narnia,
like it’s just a different reality.
Gir: No, cause then that’s like, “Oh,
mom and dad bought
this house from someone else, someone else’s
family pictures are in here.”
That
just changes it.
Wayne: No, no, you have to put some kind of
evidence
that makes it absolutely you.
Gir: Yeah, what you need is one picture of
the kid that’s
like, “Oh, my favorite son.”
And then another picture of your kid that
says, “Second favorite.”
[Baaulp, Log, Trog, and Wayne laugh]
Log: Anyways, I wanna live on a spaceship.
Baaulp: Yeah, that’d be fuckin’ sick.
Wayne: Yeah.
When I was a kid the ultimate dream was to
have
a room with no gravity.
[Baaulp laughs]
Log: I think that I’m kind of doing the
question wrong,
though, ‘cause I wanna live on like, a spaceship,
but it has to be a spaceship
in the future.
Trog: Okay.
Yeah, no, that’s fair.
I-I getcha.
Gir: Well it’s your dream house, not your
reality house.
Baaulp: Yeah, you want like Star Trek shit.
Log: It has to be a spaceship in the future,
and I have to
have a crew, and we have to sail to thousands
of wacky planets throughout the
solar system.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: You want Star Trek!
They-they made a show about
that, it’s called Star Trek!
There’s like a fuck ton of it.
Log: Yeah, but I want it to—
Wayne: Have you heard of Star Wars?
Log: —I want it to be like, for fun, and
not for terror.
Baaulp: Star Trek is fun!
Log: Not for them.
Gir: Sometimes.
Baaulp: Oh yeah, I guess a lotta people die
in Star
Trek, huh.
Trog: No, Star Trek is fun for everybody who
not in
Starfleet.
Star Trek is a show about like, a utopian
society.
Gir: That’s true.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: What about the scene where they fight
a lizard?
That
was not very utopian.
Trog: I mean, that like, just don’t join
Starfleet.
Just
live on Earth and be in a utopian society.
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: Yeah, you do what I did!
Baaulp: They’re the ones going out and like,
doing crazy
shit.
Gir: You live in the middle of nowhere in
utopia and then—
Trog: Yeah exactly.
Gir: —you just also have a holodeck in your
house.
Baaulp: Yeah, you—Yeah!
They have a holodeck on the ship,
they probably have even bigger ones on Earth!
Wayne: They probably have [unintelligible].
Baaulp: That like, tons of people can be in!
Gir: They have a holoroom.
Trog: You think you can fit a big holodeck
on a spaceship?
Imagine one the size of like uh, an airplane
hangar.
Log: But yeah, I wanna cool spaceship and
I want to have a
crew, but we’re not the Starteam, so nobody
like handles irradiated artifacts
and dies within two minutes like those guys.
[Wayne laughs]
Log: You know what I’m talking about.
Gir: No one gets killed by a sludge monster.
Baaulp: Do you sail around doing nothing?
Log: Uh, no, we-we drop on planet Me-Peemon
or whatever and
there’s little green men that uh, construct
lively, fascinating buildings that
move.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: And they teach you how to fusion dance.
Wayne: Did you have the Peemen conjured up
in your head when
you were a child as well?
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: Was that part of the plan?
Log: Well, no, ‘cause I came up with my
dream home today.
Wayne: Oh.
[Log laughs]
Wayne: Then you answered the question wrong.
Trog: No, the question is just, “What’s
your dreamhouse,” it
doesn’t say, “What’s your dreamhouse
when you were a kid.”
Wayne: I know.
This was my spin on the question, I got mad
at you earlier for doing this.
Baaulp: You guys need to crack open some architecture
books.
My dream home would be in the city, I can’t
not be in the city, it’s
just way too convenient to live in the city.
I couldn’t be like Gir and live in
the middle of nowhere.
So would be in the city, but the four outer
perimeters
of my home—there wouldn’t be a yard, it
would just be metal.
The top is open to
let like, rain and like sunlight through,
and there’s an entrance that’s like,
secret that you have to like, open it up,
and inside would be like a Japanese
pagoda ‘cause I really like water features,
I think best in the shower.
I want
like, a little like water fall thing in the
center of the home, and then like
along the perimeter of the square would be
like just rooms and shit, I don’t
know.
Trog: So you-you want a Japanese pagoda trapped
in like, a
metal dungeon?
Baaulp: Yeah, but the top is open so like,
rain and sunlight
can still shine through.
Wayne: Yeah, I can imagine this perfectly.
Trog: What is-but what is the perimeter for
then?
Wayne: For rooms!
Baaulp: I think a home like that would be
absolutely sick.
Wayne: It would, I agree.
Baaulp: And the metal’s there so that it’s
like, to everyone
else on the outside it looks scary, so no
one wants to fuck with it—
Trog: Okay.
Baaulp: —which means you can get peace and
quiet, but it’s
all nice and serene on the inside.
Gir: Too bad you live in the city!
Wayne: The other way you could approach that
as well is
like, the tower towards the end of uh, Metal
Gear Rising, where they have like,
the Japanese garden on like the top floor.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: If you had to do that in a skyscraper-type
situation,
that would also work.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: I like the idea of having it be a circle,
where you
c-you have access to that pagoda like area
from anywhere, that would be great.
Baaulp: Yeah, that’s why I like it.
I like having a nice
thing to-to look at.
Like a little bit of nature in the inside
of your home.
Gir: I-I take issue with your dreamhouse because
you want it
to be nice and peaceful and serene but you’re
still in the city, so you’re
gonna be sittin’ there thinking about all
the nice, calm things and you hear a
fucking police siren.
Wayne: No, there’s a glass dome.
Trog: Oh, it’s biodome now.
Baaulp: But why do you think it’s encased
in fucking metal.
Gir: To keep you in.
Trog: But you said the roof is open?
Wayne: Yo, let me live in Sandy’s treehouse.
Baaulp: Eh, can’t have a perfect everyth…
[laughs] Even my
perfect dream home!
[Gir laughs]
Gir: You can’t have a perfect dream home!
Trog: Even my dreamhouse isn’t perfect!
My imagination is
broken!
[Baaulp, Gir, and Wayne laugh]
Trog: Help me, please.
Wayne: I want to push the idea of a dome in
this dreamhouse.
I think any kind of house being in a dome
would be pretty sick.
Trog: That would be.
I agree.
Gir: You know what?
Yeah, take my house…
put it in a fuckin’
dome.
Wayne, laughing: Put it in—for no reason.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne, still laughing: Just a dome.
Gir: So nobody bugs me.
Baaulp, laughing: Would there be a dome over
the lake?
Trog: And Pauly Shore is there.
[Baaulp laughs harder]
Gir: There’s a door on the dome-there’s
a door on the dome.
Baaulp: Oh no, we’ve taken Gir’s dream
home and turned it
into a nightmare.
Trog: It goes from dream home to nightmare
home.
Gir: No, he’s there, but he’s in his coffin.
Wayne: Alright, so yeah, we’ve—
Baaulp: Oh, fuck.
Wayne: —we’ve talked about our dream homes,
what’s your
nightmare home?
Trog, laughing: Alright.
Nightmare home, full of used heroin
needles uh—
Wayne, laughing: Oh no.
Trog: —snakes in every pillowcase.
Wayne: Pets that I can’t remember.
Trog, laughing: All my pets that died come
back to life and
haunt me.
Gir: A box in the sewer.
Log: Every step is a new trapdoor.
[Wayne laughs]
Wayne: Oh man I would have tons trapdoors
in my dreamhouse,
though.
But I know where they are, so it’s not a
problem.
Gir: All the doors lead to somewhere different.
Trog: Carpets made out of Legos.
Baaulp: My nightmare home would be—it would
look like a
normal home at first, but you can’t pick
anything up, and then when you open
the front door it just leads into a mirror
of the same home.
[Baaulp and Trog laugh]
Wayne: Alright, alright, new important feature
in my dream
home.
I need walls that I can destroy with punches
that will rebuild
themselves.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: Okay, yeah.
No, that’s good.
I like that.
Wayne: Alright, next question.
Trog: We should just start an architecture
podcast of like,
why don’t these cool things exist?
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: [Crosstalk] Why can’t I have my dome
home?
Wayne: [Crosstalk] Why can’t I do this?
Why can’t my-why
can’t my house be in a dome and fly?
Why can’t there be a room with no gravity?
Gir: Why aren’t there self-repairing walls?
[Trog laughs]
Trog: Got a question from Hana here, who asks,
“If you had
the opportunity to see anyone in concert for
free, who would you go to see?”
Gir: Weird Al.
Baaulp: Alive or dead?
Can we pick dead people?
Trog: Y’know, there—It does not specify,
so I believe this
is as open-ended as you want it to be.
Baaulp and Gir: [Crosstalk] Oh.
Gir: Oh, Frank Sinatra.
Trog: Really.
Gir: Yeah.
Trog: Why?
Gir: I like Frank Sinatra!
Wayne: Nujabes.
Trog: That’s fair.
Wayne: My answer’s too easy, the same reason
for me.
I-I
love Nujabes and he’s dead, and I can never
see him in concert.
Trog: Yeah, that would be a really cool show.
Log: Yeah, I want to do that, too.
So, that makes it not
that funny, though.
Trog: Well, y’know, not every question has
to be
funny.
Log: There’s also not too much to discuss
about it, it’s
like, “Yeah, Nujabes is dead, and he’s
great.”
Wayne: Because I like him.
Log: Yeah.
Wayne: Like, yeah.
Log: I mean, no-no argument there.
Trog: Not every question has to take thirty
minutes to
answer ‘cause we go off on wild tangents.
Sometimes people might just want a
damn answer to their question!
Wanye: [Crosstalk] It’s true!
Trog: Baaulp, what’s your answer?
Who would you like to see
in concert for free?
Baaulp: Devo.
Trog: Devo?
That would be good.
Wayne: Ohh, that’s not bad.
Trog: Like, prime-prime time Devo.
Baaulp: Yeah, like Devo when like, they were
all-I mean,
they’re old, and like—Well, actually two
of them died, so-which is like, also a
good reason.
‘Cause two of them died, I don’t think
they’re really
touring-gonna be touring anymore, but they—Like,
even as old men, they go
fucking hard.
Wayne: And then on the opposite side of things,
I saw a
Journey-uh, a Journey reunion concert and
uh, they did not go hard.
[Trog laughs]
Gir: Aw, they-are they really not that good
anymore?
Wayne, laughing: They did not have it in them
anymore.
Trog: My answer—
Wayne, in a singing voice: Juke Box Hero.
Trog: —also not very funny, and maybe a
little strange but,
honestly, the first thing that came to my
mind was Neil Cicierega.
I would like
to see Neil Cicierega in concert.
Wayne: [Crosstalk] Oh, yeah.
Trog: I really liked his last Lemon Demon
album, and he has
a bunch of funny mashups that would probably
be a fun little thing to play
live.
I think it’d be a fun concert, all around.
Gir: I think I’m old.
Baaulp: It’s okay that we answered this
really quick, but I
do have a quick tangent that I really just
thought of.
Why didn’t we pick like,
an ancient thing?
Like, can you imagine like—I pick cavemen!
I want to see what
a caveman concert was like!
Wayne: The-the first musician.
Log: I thought about talking about cavemen,
but Nujabes was the
obvious choice.
Could hear something that I’ve never heard
before, and nobody’s
heard before—
Gir: I want to see Mozart.
Log: —could be just stupid as fuck, but…
Wayne: I want-I want to turn this back around
again.
So, we
picked artists that are dead.
Trog: Well, I didn’t.
Wayne: If we have these magic concert powers,
we could also
pick artists that don’t exist.
Baaulp: Oh shit.
Wayne: But-but because that would just be
stupid, ‘cause we
can just say whatever we want—
Baaulp: Zarknon the Embarrassed.
Wayne: I want the guy who sings Scrod on YouTube.
Trog: Oooh, yeah.
Wayne, singing: Scrod.
Log: I’ll tell you, I’ve looked at his
channel since then,
you don’t want to see him in concert.
Trog: Oh no.
Wayne: Oh, really?
Log: Yeah.
I mean like, I can’t… really describe
what his
songs are about now, uh, one of them was about
how Donald Trump Jr. was a robot
baby or something.
Trog: Alrighty.
Wayne: Well then I’ll-I’ll change my answer,
and I want the
guys who did Junior Spesh.
Log and Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: And these will both be in the description
if you have no idea what I’m talking about,
uh, these will be part of the Videos of the
Times for our description.
Gir: I want Scary Al Yankovic.
[Trog, Baaulp, and Wayne laugh]
Gir: It’s one of the alternate universe
versions of Weird Al
Yankovic.
[Wayne laughs]
Wayne: What does he sing about?
Gir: I don’t know but it’s really scary.
Wayne, laughing: The scariest concert imaginable.
He’s just
got knives and he’s throwing them into the
crowd and he’s wailing.
Gir: Yeah.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: Every universe has their own version
of Al Yankovic.
We
got weird, someone got scary, someone’s
got sad—
Wayne: And he’s also not necessarily good,
either.
He’s
singing Michael Jackson, “I’m Bad,”
like, y’know Weird Al Yankovic has, “I’m
Fat,” he’s just going, “I’m scary!
I’m scary!”
And he’s throwing knives into
the crowds.
[Everyone laughs]
Gir: No, he’s singing, “I’m Bad,”
but there’s no music, he’s
just on screen—on-on stage screaming, “I’m
bad!
I’m bad!”
[Wayne chants with Gir]
Gir: Everyone’s crying.
Wayne: One bad guy up here.
This is kind of similar to the
Hitman question earlier, but Frisbee, our
good friend Frisbee, father Frisbee
asks, “If there was a WayneRadioTV battle
royale, who would win?”
Gir: Well, y’never know, it’s a battle
royale.
Trog: Hmm…
Who all is in it?
Like, everyone who’s ever been
on a stream?
Wayne: That’s the problem, is, I think the
crew, which
is—yeah, the stream crew, I guess.
Trog: That’s like a-that’s y’know, that’s
a pretty decent
number of people.
Baaulp: I would win.
Trog: Oh.
Wow.
Wayne: Why?
How could you best me?
Baaulp: Uhh…
Gir: He’d beat you.
Baaulp: ‘Cause I’d find a gun before you
[laughs] and shoot
you.
[Wayne and Trog laugh]
Wayne, still laughing: I guess.
Y’know, I guess.
I suck at
battle royale games, so…
Trog: Yeah I was about to say, I don’t think
I would last
very long.
Wayne: If it’s like that kind of battle
royale—
Baaulp: If we’re thinking like Fortnite
and PUBG then I
mean, like, I found a gun, I-I shoot you.
[Wayne laughs]
Wayne: Damn!
Baaulp: It-it’s not even skill!
Gir: I found a gun.
I shoot you.
Wayne: Y’know you-this is like playground
rules, you said
that first, so I can’t like, I can’t say
like, “No, but I picked up a gun and
got you, too!”
Like that’s-that’d be bad manners.
Gir: But I-I shot you harder!
Log: Yeah, well, you could say that you deflected
it.
Wayne, laughing: Oh, I deflected it.
Oh, I drank a chug
juice.
[Log, Baaulp and Wayne laugh]
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] I get in a Jeep and drive
away!
Trog: [Crosstalk] Look, we’re not going
to devolve this
podcast into roleplaying a battle royale,
okay?
Gir: I would hide, and then wait for the last
person.
Wayne: Alright, now I-now I-now I-Now I unsheath
my blade of
a thousand lights.
Baaulp: My dad bought me V-Bucks.
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: Oh, that just makes you look cool.
You don’t get an
advantage from V-Bucks, you fuck.
Trog: That’s what you think, that’s what
they try-that’s
what they try to tell you, but—
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: —the V-Bucks are important to your
power.
Gir: You think I wear this chicken suit for
fun?
Wayne: I think Scorpy would be very hard to
deal
with.
Baaulp: Oh, yeah.
Scorpy would like, set up a kill house.
Wayne: Yeah.
His tactics would be very unorthodox.
Trog: His level of guerrilla warfare would
be unmatched.
He
would attack you in ways that you-we can’t
even comprehend at this moment.
Gir: I think he’d get confused very easily
and then we could
kill him.
Trog: I got a question from MissFroggish here,
who asks,
“What’s the most bizarre thing you’d
willingly eat?”
Wayne: Shampoo.
Baaulp: I’d have to abstain from this question.
Wayne: Where do we draw the line?
Trog: You draw the line.
It’s what’s the most bizarre thing you
would willingly eat!
Gir: Hmm.
Baaulp: I will say this, let’s limit it
to [sighs] to food,
‘cause then—
Gir: Nonpoisonous substances.
Baaulp: We—If we don’t to that then we’ll
get like, a Mega
64 Christmas cast question where it’s like,
“Oh, I-yeah, I’d drink my own pee.”
Wayne: I feel like we’ve answered this already.
Trog: Have we answered this already?
Gir: I don’t think so.
Wayne: I feel like we talked about a very
similar question,
‘cause I remember we-we were talking about
like, eating poop, at one point.
[Gir and Baaulp laugh]
Gir: That was just a conversation we had.
Wayne: Maybe…
Gir: That wasn’t recorded.
Trog: I will say that everybody here, I’m
pretty sure, has
gone on record in saying that they would eat
some amount of raw beef for
some amount of money.
[Wayne and Baaulp laugh]
Gir: Oh, I would not.
Trog: That might just be the blanket answer
for this one.
Baaulp: That is true.
It was not recorded anywhere, but what
was the conversation we had?
I remember saying like, I’d rather eat like
a
pound of raw meat for twenty bucks.
Trog: No, I asked, “You get twenty dollars
for every ounce
of raw meat that you eat.
How much could you do before you had to stop?
And if
you throw up, you get no money.”
Gir: I would decline.
Trog: That-that was the question.
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] One pound
Wayne: [Crosstalk] A pound.
Trog: [Crosstalk] That was a hypothetical
question I
proposed like, 6 months ago.
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] Two pounds.
Wayne: I don’t think you could do two pounds.
I could do a
pound, I don’t think you could do two pounds.
Baaulp: Mayb—I might be able to do two pounds.
Gir: I believe Baaulp could do two.
Wayne: I don’t know.
Trog: Without throwing up?
Wayne: Like, is there a time limit?
There was a time
limit, wasn’t there?
Baaulp: There wasn’t a time limit.
Gir: Two pounds isn’t that much.
Wayne: Two pounds is a lot of beef!
Trog: There wasn’t a time limit, but it
was in one sitting
and you can’t throw up.
Like, you can’t get up and do something,
you have to
sit there.
Wayne: Gir, Gir.
Most burgers are a-are like a half pound.
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: Like quarter pounder to a half pound,
you are not
eating two pounds of beef!
Gir: Imagine those hotdog eating contests
where people are
eating like, fifteen pounds of food.
Wayne: Yeah, and they’re cooked, and those
people are also
trained, professional eaters.
I’m asking you in your current state—
Baaulp: Those people must be rich.
Wayne: You don’t have the hyperbolic time
chamber in this
fucking scenario!
Gir: I wouldn’t do it to begin with!
I ain’t eatin’ no
fuckin’ raw meat!
Trog: No, you have to do this tomorrow.
Wayne: YOU NEED TO DO IT NOW!
When you answer this question,
when you give me-when you give me your answer,
the beef is going to materialize
in front of you—
Trog, laughing: It’s going to teleport—
Wayne: —you have to do it right now!
Gir: Well it’s a good thing I’m declining!
I ain’t eating no
raw beef!
Trog: Alright, there we go.
Now we know Gir’s answer.
Wayne: Okay, well then [laughs] well then
no meat will
appear on your desk today.
Gir: Thank god.
Trog: For the record, I would also not do
this for any
amount of money.
Gir, laughing: Yeah.
[Wayne joins in on the laughter]
Wayne: I think it’s only me and Baaulp.
[Gir sighs]
Baaulp: I think—Aw, man.
I would choose not to, but if
someone—If I was—If it was like a hypothetical
situation where I had to,
I mean go-go for the gold, right?
Let’s see if I can down two pounds!
[Laughs]
Trog: Well, that’s the thing.
It’s not a situation where you
have to, it’s a situation where you get
paid to.
Gir: You have to take this money for eating
this
meat.
Log: I don’t know.
I don’t think I really need to be eating
raw meat.
Trog: Exactly.
Log: If we’re talking hypotheticals, I can
just get my
spaceship crew—
Baaulp: Have them eat it!
Log: I can just get Beemo from my spaceship
crew who is a
caveman who eats raw meat—
Trog: [Crosstalk] No you’re crossing the-the
hypothetical
streams, this isn’t-this isn’t canon anymore.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: Question’s over.
Wayne: Our friend Lauren asks, “What was
your favorite toy
as a wee child?”
Trog: Hmm.
Baaulp: I... really liked Legos.
Gir: [Crosstalk] That’s actually a question.
Baaulp: Like, I-I-I—At-at a certain point
before I was too
young for video games, to have like a lot
of video games, I would always just
ask for Legos.
I loved that shit.
I loved bricks.
Gir: I gotta go with Bionicles.
Like, to this day I would
still like—the thought of me getting a new
Bionicle, even like at twenty-five,
for Christmas is like, wow I would love that.
Baaulp: Dude, you should totally just buy
Bionicles for
yourself.
If it still genuinely excites you—
Trog: They’re not easy to get anymore.
Gir: They’re not—If I wanted one of the
old ones like, when
I was actually a child, it would be like,
two hundred dollars.
Baaulp: [Crosstalk[ Ohhhh.
Trog: Yeah, those things are expensive.
Baaulp: Oh fuck.
Gir: It’s a Lego product, like, it’s not
cheap.
Wayne: I like, disproportionately valued a
toy if it was
from a video game when I was a kid.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] What do you mean?
Wayne: I had a Banjo-Kazooie uh, like, stuffed
animal—
Baaulp: Ohhh.
Wayne: —that was my favorite.
Trog: [Crosstalk] Oh, that’s sick.
I want one of those right
now.
Wayne: It was so cool!
I actually—No, it was just Banjo,
‘cause I lost the backpack.
Trog: Ah.
Gir: Oh no.
Wayne: It started as Banjo-Kazooie, but at
some point I lost
the backpack, but honestly, like that’s
fine.
Log, laughing: Kazooie died.
[Gir and Wayne laugh]
Trog: Oh no.
Gir: Your parents never told you, but…
Wayne: Hey, the child inside of me is really
upset, they
were just in split mode.
They used the split power up in Twooie.
Trog: Yeah.
Log: Forever.
[Wayne, Gir, and Trog laugh]
Gir: They split up.
Wayne: Sometimes partnerships don’t last.
Log, laughing: That’s what your mom told
you—that’s what
your mom told you whenever your Kazooie died.
[Gir laughs]
Wayne, laughing: My Kazooie.
Gir: Oh no.
Baaulp: Does that mean you uh, you loved that
Chunky Kong
car just as much?
Or van?
Wayne: Yeah, I love it so much I don’t know
where it is
right now.
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Log: Ah, where’s your copy of Elite Beat
Agents?
Wayne: That is gone, I’m pretty sure.
No, I think I
have that in a box somewhere.
Log, you should elaborate on that story and
why-why you brought that up.
Log: I’ve only been to Connecticut once,
to see Wayne.
I’ve
seen Wayne more than once, but I’ve only
been to his house once.
And whenever was
at his house, we went down to his bedroom,
and we were—all of us, there were
like five of us, we’re all just chillin’
down there, and then I looked at his
shelves.
His shelves were just barren except for a
copy of Elite Beat Agents
for the Nintendo DS.
Wayne: Outside of the case.
[Wayne and Trog laugh]
Log: Yeah, it’s just on its own.
Trog: That is an important-that is an important
detail to
add.
Gir: Wayne, what the fuck?
Log: Just outside the case, on its own, only
thing on
the shelf.
Wayne: Those shelves were unorganized, and
to be fair, the
other-the other shelves did have some things
on them.
You are-you are
exaggerating a little bit.
Gir: They sounded pretty organized considering
there was one
thing on them!
Wayne: Yes.
One item per shelf, that is a rule, and it
doesn’t matter how small the item is [laughs].
The, no, I don’t know, man.
It
just happened, I was done playing it and I’m
like, “This will go on my shelf
today.”
Gir: “I will put this up here today.”
Baaulp: “I won’t put it back in the box!”
Trog: “And I don’t have the case anymore.”
Wayne, laughing: I don’t know, I couldn’t
give you my
legitimate reasoning for why that was there.
Gir: You didn’t have a legitimate reason,
you just did it.
Trog: Exactly.
Wayne: Yes, but it was a very funny—you
pointed it out to me
and I was just like, “Oh, fuck you.
Fuck off.”
Trog: What constitutes a toy, because—
Gir: Oh, come on.
Baaulp: We’re about to get a good answer.
Trog: —if we’re counting video games as
toys, then like, my
Nintendo 64 would definitely be—
Gir: Video games aren’t toys.
Baaulp: We’ll say for this it has to be
a toy that’s not a
video game.
Trog: Then yeah, I would say like, probably,
also—not
Bionicles specifically, I loved Bionicles
and I still do, but like any sort of
like, building toy.
I had ‘em all.
I had like, Bionicles, I had K’Nex, I had
Legos, I had these weird—I don’t even
know what they’re called, they were like
super weird shaped the gimmick was that like,
you could pull on them and
they would like, look different.
I don’t even know, I’m probably describing
this in a really stupid way—
Gir: Oh, dicks.
Trog: —but, I literally don’t know what
those are called.
Yeah, I had a bunch of building toys as a
kid, and honestly, I wish I had Legos
right now.
I kinda want Legos for Christmas.
Wayne: Alright, monkey’s paw.
You get two Legos, like—
Trog: Ah, perfect.
Wayne: —like two bricks.
Baaulp: Every time I’ve gone to a Lego store
they got you
down.
They know what they’re doing.
There are like, adult Lego kits where
instead of just like, “Oh, here’s a spaceship
or whatever.”
It’s like, it’s
like monuments or like, cars or stuff—like
real deal stuff for adults—
Trog: Hey, I would absolutely build a spaceship
over like, a
monument [laughs].
Baaulp: But they’re so expensive.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: There was one for the Eiffel Tower
that looked
really cool, but it was like fifty bucks!
Gir: Yeah, Lego ain’t cheap, man.
Baaulp: I guess not.
Trog: Yeah, but building toys, many an hour
as a child were
spent playing with my Bionicles, listening
to the Sonic Adventure Sound Test in
my bedroom.
Wayne: Dude, Sound Tests were sick.
Trog: It was the best.
I just had all the songs in Sonic
Adventure, aw man, it was like my own jukebox,
it was great.
Wayne: When I was a kid, I always though that
like, video
game-based toys were hard to find, that you
like wouldn’t just find them
regularly in the store, but I had a surprising
amount of them.
I had a lot of
Sonic toys.
Specifically, a separate set of Sonic Adventure
1 and Sonic
Adventure 2 toys.
They were different because one had Shadow.
Trog: How sick.
Wayne: And the other one didn’t have S—The
other one was
just Sonic.
Okay no, acutal-actual favorite toy, E-102
toy.
I actually had
that.
Trog: Really?
Wayne: It was sick.
Yes!
Trog: That does sound pretty sick.
Wayne: Log, what’re yours?
Log: When I was a kid I had a stuffed bear
named Happy and a
stuffed Pikachu, and they were my two best
friends.
Trog: Ah, that’s awesome.
Wayne, chuckling: Great name.
Baaulp: Aww.
Wayne: Great name.
Trog: I used to have a shit ton of Beanie
Babies as a kid.
Gir: Same.
Trog: I don’t even know where I got ‘em
from.
Gir: I still have all of them, and they’re
in a sack
somewhere in my closet.
Log, laughing: You’re shitting on the name
of a stuffed
bear.
[Wayne laughs and Trog joins in]
Log: Yeah, I’m pretty sure that I still
have those guys.
Well, actually not the Pikachu.
The Pikachu got mauled by an animal and we
tried—
Trog: Oh no.
Log: —we tried to repair it, but it just
wasn’t the same.
Trog: Aww.
Wayne: I had a Pikachu that was like a stuffed
animal with
like, a mechanical bit inside of it and you
would like, squeeze its cheeks and
it would like, light up and go like, “Pikachu!”
It was great.
Gir: It would electrocute you.
Wayne: Yeah, it had static shock features
[laughs].
Gir: They could probably get away with that
these days.
Wayne: Yeah.
Trog: The other thing that I uh-that I had
as a kid that I
really liked were Yu-Gi-Oh cards.
I was big into Yu-Gi-Oh.
Wayne: Yes.
Trog: Definitely didn’t know how to play
the game but—
Baaulp: Same.
Gir: Same.
Trog: —damn did those cards look sick.
Gir: We were all the same that way.
Baaulp: I had so many Yu-Gi-Oh cards.
Wayne: This is actually a great topic because
someone has a
Yu-Gi-Oh related question that like, was a
little bit too specific but we can
like talk about Yu-Gi-Oh!
When you were a kid, did you understand the
rules of
Yu-Gi-Oh?
Gir: Barely.
Baaulp: In theory, yes, but not really.
Trog: Nope!
Not at all.
Well like, barely.
Wayne: When I was a kid no one understood
it, and some of
the cards were so complicated that I could
just bullshit whatever I wanted.
Trog: Yep.
Wayne: There was a card that had a picture
that was like, a
bunch of scrolls.
It was like scrolls flying around in an interdimensional
space, and the text was—it had something
to do with like, adding a card onto
another card, and the block of text was so
big that you could barely read it,
and it was too complex for me or any of my
other friends to understand, so
anything I played it I’d be just like, “Yeah,
I know what that one does.
I
will-I will put this on my Blue Eyes White
Dragon and I can add any
monster card to this card, and you just have
to add up their attacks, and I can
do this however many times I want.”
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: And I did that and would win all the
time.
Trog: Yeah.
I understood how to win the game because that
part was pretty much the only part of the
rules that actually like—
Baaulp: It’s easy, you just have to destroy
the other
player.
Trog: Yeah, you just bring the other player’s
life points to
zero.
That’s how it works in the show, so that’s
how it works in the game.
I
totally didn’t understand how trading card
games worked on any level, and I
would think that it’s like, “Oh I can
just like, discard any cards I want if I
don’t want them, and then just keep drawing
cards from my deck, right?”
[Wayne and Baaulp laugh]
Trog: Like, I didn’t understand the concept
of like, “Oh,
you draw one a turn, you can’t just throw
cards away,” all that stuff was too
much for my child brain.
Gir: I mostly just didn’t understand the
concept of uh,
strategy.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne, laughing: Yeah.
Trog: That’s definitely…
yeah.
Wayne: It was get the big numbers out!
Gir: Yeah, I would get a card and be like,
“I use this.”
And
they’re like, “You can’t use that.”
“Oh, well…
I don’t know.
Your turn then.”
[Wayne and Trog laugh]
Wayne: Yeah.
No, one of the things we would do—So in
uh, in
Magic the Gathering, I mean, as far as I know
from like just osmosis from my
friends Mira and Baaulp, you-you can draft.
There’s like a draft kind of like,
playstyle where you—
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] Yeah, you open up packs.
Wayne: —you draft from like, a pool of cards,
you pick your
deck.
What me and my friends would do, I had a lot
of Yu-Gi-Oh cards, and we
would just put them in a bin, shake them around,
dump them on the floor, and we
would pretty much do draft but with no limitations.
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: So it’d just be like—we’d just
have these giant
decks of like, anything we wanted, and it
was great.
Trog: That sounds fun!
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: It’s called no holds drafts.
Baaulp: It’s expensive to get all the cards
together, but
there’s a way to play Magic called cube,
where you just get all your favorite
cards, you like, come up with deck archetypes,
and you just put all of them
together and you make artificial booster packs
and keep you drafting those and
playing over and over again.
It’s probably one of the best ways to play
if it
wasn’t like, so expensive to put together.
Trog: Whenever I was a kid I used to play
basketball cards
as if they were a card game.
[Everyone laughs]
Baaulp: Oh damn.
Wayne: I play Michael Jordan!
Trog: No, like.
No joke, literally!
Gir: In attack mode!
Trog: Literally, like, I like, because my
dad is a coach
like, for a—like a middle school coach,
and they would do basketball camps every
summer, and every summer I would go to them
and get a shit ton of basketball
cards ‘cause they would just give them out
to all the kids, and so I ended up
with a fuck ton of basketball cards.
And, being a kid that loves Yu-Gi-Oh, but
doesn’t have a lot of Yu-Gi-Oh cards, but
does have ten times as many
basketball cards, it was time for me to make
my own version of Yu-Gi-Oh where
Michael Jordan was the Blue Eyes White Dragon.
[Everyone laughs]
Baaulp: Holy shit.
Wayne: See, I like the idea that you’d be
playing a game of
Yu-Gi-Oh with your friends and you just sneak
a Michael Jordan card in your
deck.
Trog, laughing: You just throw that one out.
[Log laughs]
Log: I specifically didn’t understand the
value in sports
cards because they didn’t have moves and
effects.
Trog: Yeah, they didn’t do anything!
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: I was the same way!
It was like, what makes one of
these more valuable, it doesn’t matter.
Log: Yeah, I mean, I—there’s no game.
There’s no—They don’t
have HP, they don’t have attack, what can
I use them for?
Wayne: I mean, we were like—we’re-we’re—there’s
a little bit
of like, age range here, but we were born
before the time of like, the strictly
collectible—
Trog and Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: —like, things you can get into.
Like, like, none of
us had pogs, right?
Trog and Baaulp: No.
Gir: Not on purpose.
Trog: We like, really just missed the boat
on pogs.
Pogs was like, the generation right before
us.
Wayne: Pogs sounded pretty great, honestly.
Trog: And every time I hear someone talk about
them it’s
like, damn I would’ve fucking loved pogs
as a kid.
Wayne: Yeah.
Trog: Sad that I missed out on that.
Wayne: And I was mistaken, there was a game
to pogs.
Like,
you had to-you had to slam them on the table,
and try to take other people’s
pogs.
Trog: [Crosstalk] Yeah, you like try to flip
them.
You play
for keeps.
Baaulp: Pogs is cool from the standpoint that
the game was
the game.
And what your pogs were were purely cosmetic,
so like, you could
really like, let your character shine through,
y’know.
Trog: Yeah, no, that’s the cool thing about
pogs, is that
pogs were literally just a piece of cardboard
with something printed on the
front—
Baaulp: Yeah, exactly.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: —so like, you could have pogs for
like, any possible
franchise that you like.
Wayne: Didn’t they have like a, lamination
on them, or
something?
Weren’t they like a [unintelligible] of
sorts?
Gir: [Crosstalk] Yeah.
Trog: [Crosstalk] Yeah.
Gir: [Crosstalk] Like a thin plastic film.
Trog: Yeah, yeah.
I mean, they were like—
Wayne: ‘Cause you could get like a pog maker.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: Yeah, I remember them.
Yeah.
Gir: I’ve collected Pokémon cards for the
sake of collecting
the cards.
Not because I wanted to play that godawful
game.
Trog: I did Pokémon for a little bit.
Wayne: You treated Pokémon cards like basketball
cards.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: I feel like the thing with Pokémon
cards—they fell,
somehow, into a pit where they were treated
like that.
I never—I had tons of Pokémon
cards, never played the game, ever.
Trog: Yeah, I don’t know.
Gir: Well you collect Pokémon in the Pokémon
games, so I
mean…
Trog: That’s fair.
Wayne: Yeah, but you fight with them.
Gir: No, I don’t.
Trog: Yeah, but you can also just collect
them just to have
them.
Like, you gotta catch ‘em all.
That’s what they say.
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: I like to look at the pictures.
It’s not ‘gotta fight
with ‘em all’.
Wayne: And the art on Pokémon cards is pretty
good.
I-I
really like the old Pokémon card art.
Baaulp: I can’t let Log’s idea go.
I would play the shit
out of a card game where the cards were like,
fuck it.
Pick a sport y’know,
basketball, football, just make a card game
where are the cards are like, pro
players, but don’t have the game replicate
like, how a normal football,
basketball, hockey game would progress.
Instead, structure it like a fantasy
battle, like—
[Trog laughs]
Baaulp: —Okay, I-I play two uh, Larry Bird—I
play two Magic
Johnson’s uh, fetch-fetch a-fetch a [laughs]
Michael Jordan number one, special
summon.
Wayne: I want a scry to find LeBron James.
Trog: Yeah.
It’s kinda ironic, because yeah, as a kid,
a
basketball card has no intrinsic worth because
it has no statistics tied to it
that are part of a game, but in reality it’s
the opposite.
A basketball card is
one hundred percent tied to the worth of the
literal human it is based off of.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Gir: Yeah.
Trog: And a Yu-Gi-Oh card is whatever Konami
decides to
print on it.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: It’s completely arbitrary.
Baaulp: Alright, the point of this deck is
to get as many
Shaqs into your graveyard as you can, and
then bring them back.
[Trog and Wayne laugh]
Gir: Kill Shaq as much as you can.
Wayne: The Shaq zombie deck.
Baaulp, laughing: It’s a-it’s a basketball
card game but
there’s a graveyard.
[Wayne, Trog, and Log laugh]
Wayne, laughing: The players are dying.
What happens when
you exile Michael Jordan?
Trog: He disappears.
Pops out of existence.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: The funny thing is that’s just called
the bench, but
the graveyard is a graveyard.
[Wayne and Log laugh]
Wayne: I use a—I use Hierophant’s Cage
to summon a minotaur
to hold Michael Jordan on the bench.
[Trog, Log, and Wayne laugh]
Trog: KingMusicManz asks, “Who is your best
impersonation?”
Gir: That’s hard because it’s up to someone
else to tell you
it’s good.
If you’re like certain your impersonation’s
good, it’s probably not.
Wayne: I think the only one that I’ve ever
done that any
of you have ever told me was even remotely
okay is Agent 47.
Trog: Your Agent 47 is pretty good, I like
it.
It’s
definitely entertaining.
Baaulp: This question is weird.
Is this supposed to be our
last question?
Trog and Gir: Yeah.
Trog: I want to go out on somebody’s amazing
impersonation.
Baaulp: Oh.
Wayne: Uh, Log—Ohhh, Log does an amazing
Yajirobe
impersonation.
Gir: Does he?
Log: That makes no sense to me because I don’t
know what
Yajirobe actually sounds like.
[Trog and Wayne laugh]
Baaulp: Log, show me your imp—your amazing
Yajirobe
impression!
Log: Uhh… here, let me-let me see if I can
try it.
Log, as Yajirobe: Hey!
This is the voice I make
when I try to be Kuwabara, but apparently
that’s Yajirobe, too!
Wayne: It’s the same voice!
Trog: It’s the same voice, yeah.
Gir: Eh, kinda.
Wayne, as Agent 47: Hello, Yajirobe.
Log, as Yajirobe: I’ve never heard Yajirobe
in my life!
Gir: Look, I’m a Dragon Ball aficionado,
and I gotta say,
that’s alright.
Log: Yeah, well..
Wayne: It’s not bad.
Gir: You could do better, but you could do
worse.
Log: I-I wouldn’t know.
Wayne: Let’s do a fanon scene with Yajirobe
and Agent 47.
Go.
Wayne, as Agent 47: Hello, Yajirobe.
Log, as Yajirobe: Hey!
You’ve got my suit on!
Wayne, as Agent 47: Care for a—
Log, as Yajirobe: Take it off and give it
to me!
Wayne, as Agent 47: Care for a treat?
Log, as Yajirobe: ...Yes.
[Baaulp and Trog laugh]
Gir, as Yajirobe: I’m ready to eat, man!
Trog: And scene.
Wayne, as Agent 47: It’s like a [unintelligible]
treat.
Gir, as Yajirobe: [Crosstalk] Put food in
my mouth!
I need
to use the bathroom!
[Log and Trog laugh]
Log, as Yajirobe: Hey, what are these scissors
doing on the
floor?
Gir, as Yajirobe: Is that a coin?
Log, as Yajirobe: Guess I-guess I better pick
them up!
Wayne: I can’t—I mean, if I’m in character
I can’t say
anything because Agent 47 doesn’t really
talk that often.
Gir, as Agent 47: Hey, go pick up that coin
off the floor
for me.
Trog: Yeah, what if that, what if every time
Agent 47 threw
a coin he just also said like, “Hey, can
you pick that up for me?”
Gir, as Agent 47: Could you grab that for
me?
Trog, as Agent 47: I just dropped this.
Baaulp, in a British accent: ‘Ello, what’s
this?
A pair o’
scissors on the ground?
Gir: Oh, that’s my favorite character!
Trog: Alright, and who is this?
What is this new character?
Is this Gordon Ramsay?
Wayne: That’s Agent 47’s uh, commissioner.
Log: That-that’s Ms. Burnwood.
Trog: Oh, okay.
Gir: Ah, of course.
Gir, as Yoda: [Clears throat]
Wayne: Everyone can do a Yoda impression.
Gir, as Yoda: Very good.
Gir: I know.
Baaulp, in a British accent: And what’s
this green creature
doing here?
Gir, as Yoda: [Laughs]
Wayne, as Agent 47: That is my pet, Yoda.
Gir, as Yoda: I am—Pet I am not.
Baaulp, in a British accent: Agent 47 this
is—a, this
is—This creature is disgusting—
Gir, as Yoda: Pick me up?
Baaulp, in a British accent: Dispose of him!
Gir, as Yoda: Fuck you.
Wayne, as Agent 47: Okay.
I will use—I will use the fiber
wire.
On Yoda.
Gir, as Yoda: [Makes choking sounds]
Wayne, as Agent 47: Die, bitch [breaks character
and
laughs].
[Baaulp and Wayne laugh]
Gir, as Yoda: No, ah!
No!
Oh my god, is that Agent Buddy?
Gir: Now it’s just Grover!
Gir, as Grover: Is that Agent Buddy?
Elmo?
Baaulp: Grover, meet Yajirobe!
Gir, as Grover: Hello!
Wayne, as Agent 47: I-I-I-I kill Grover and
take his
clothes.
Trog: [Unintelligible]
Gir, as Grover: There is an assassin at the
end of this
book!
Log, in a southern(?) accent: Alright, Agent
47, I need you to
uh, [smacks lips] take Yoda and uh, you gotta-you
gotta get rid of the body,
right?
[Everyone laughs]
Gir: Who’s this?
Log, as ???: You gotta, push him over the
ledge.
Gir: Oh, is that supposed to be fucking Karl
Pilkington?
Log: I don’t-I don’t know.
You don’t tell me—you shouldn’t
have asked this question.
I can’t [unintelligible].
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: Oh!
Kermit the Frog!
When did you get here?
Gir, as Kermit: Oh, I don’t know!
Wayne, as Agent 47: Agent 47.
Trog: [Crosstalk] D…does Agent 47 just say
his own name a
lot?
Gir, as Kermit: [Crosstalk] Hi-ho, Agent 47.
Baaulp: He’s like a Pokémon!
[Trog laughs]
Gir, as Agent 47: 47.
47.
Wayne, as Agent 47: I’m sorry.
Sorry, sometimes I think out
loud.
[Laughs]
[Trog and Gir laugh]
Gir: That’s perfect for an assassin!
Baaulp: It would never happen, but an Agent
47 like, map
that’s just Sesame Street would be so good.
Wayne: Oh yeah, my favorite game, Agent 47.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: I think one of them was called that.
Gir: I was about to say, I’m pretty sure
one was
called Agent 47.
Log, in a deep voice: Woah, dude, I just got
the new Hitman!
Hitman 47!
Wait a minute, that’s not right!
How do—Oh no!
[Wayne and Gir laugh]
Baaulp: Yoda, what’s the game actually called?
Gir, as Yoda: Hm, I don’t know.
Trog: Scatman John, when did you get here!
Gir, as Scatman John: Scat-a-daba-da-be.
[Log laughs]
Baaulp: Oh no, Scatman John, what are you
doing to the
younglings?
[Everyone laughs]
Gir: Alright, I don’t think—we need to
move on from there.
[Baaulp sings a repetitive tune for several
seconds]
Trog: Oh, Scatman John you’re here just
in time, Michael
Jackson just showed up!
Wayne, as Michael Jackson: Hee-hee!
[Everyone yells OHHHH!]
[Baaulp resumes singing the same repetitive
tune]
Baaulp, in a British accent: Oh, you won’t
best me MJ, I have
the high ground!
Gir, as Yoda: You will not win.
[Log and Trog laugh]
Gir, as Yoda: Win you will not.
Log, as MJ: You underestimate my power!
Gir, as Yoda: You underestimate…
me!
Log: So, in short, to answer the question—
Wayne, as Harry Potter: [Crosstalk] It’s
me, Harry Potter, I
am a member of the WayneRadioTV podcast!
[Laughs] I like, I can’t do any
impression for long enough.
Log: [Crosstalk] —we don’t know how—we
don’t know—we don’t
know how to be any character.
We can’t impress upon any character, so…
Baaulp, in a British accent: Flipendo!
Wayne: Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Don’t—You’re not giving us enough
credit.
Your Yajirobe is legitimately good.
My Agent 47—
Baaulp: Flipendo!
Wayne: —and Baaulp’s [laughs] Flipendo!
Trog: And Baaulp’s anything he says ever.
Log, laughing: Flipendo!
Gir: And I got nothin’.
Wayne: This is a fuckin’ mess.
Thank you so much—
Trog, as Mario: [Crosstalk] It’s a me!
Mario!
Wayne: Thank you so much—
Baaulp, in a British accent: [Crosstalk] You
won’t best—Hmm,
you won’t best me Harry Potter, I have the
high ground!
Gir, as Mario: Mario!
Baaulp, in a British accent: Flipendo!
Wayne: It’s me, Wario!
Gir: I can do a—oh, no!
I can do an impersonation!
Gir, as Donkey Kong taking damage: Ooh.
Wayne, laughing: He can!
He actually does a really good one
of those.
Wayne: Thank you so much for listening to
Where Do We Begin.
We didn’t know where we’d start, but we
know where we finish.
If you like this podcast, subscribe to the
RSS feed for more.
Uh, you can find us once
again, if you’re listening to us through
some weird means, we’re on Spotify, wayneradiotv.podbean.com,
soon to be on iTunes and GooglePlay, as well
as maybe
the WayneRadioTV YouTube channel.
If you want to ask questions, uh, join the
WayneRadioTV Discord, which will be in the
description of this podcast, or—did
you set up an e-mail, Baaulp?
Baaulp: Uh, I can.
Trog: We will set up an e-mail, and Baaulp
will edit in what
that e-mail address is riiiiight here.
Baaulp: Hey, Baaulp here, with a message from
their future,
but still your past.
You can now e-mail your questions to wheredowebeginqa@gmail.com.
That’s wheredowebeginqa, all one word, lowercase,
at gmail.com.
If you don’t
feel like joining the Discord to ask your
questions, or if you just want to ask
your questions anonymously, you can now send
your questions to that e-mail
address.
Thank you!
Wayne: And that’s our e-mail!
Great name, huh?
I love it.
I’m gonna be sending e-mails to that tonight,
myself.
Uh, but, yeah, make sure
to tell your friends about this podcast if
you enjoyed it.
Make sure to follow
the WayneRadioTV Twitch channel as well, and
any of the other social media
accounts linked in the description below.
Uh, any closing words?
Gir: Can’t wait to e-mail myself.
Baaulp, in a British accent: Flipendo!
Gir, in a high voice: Flipendo!
Wayne, as Agent 47: Goodnight, everyone.
Flipendo.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir, as Yoda: Goodnight, everybody.
Someone using a high-tone voice pitcher, possibly
Trog:
Goodnight!
Wayne, as Agent 47: Flipendo, again.
I throw a soda now.
Baaulp: I think it-it’s over.
Wayne, as Agent 47: No, I’m gonna throw
more soda.
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Trog: We’re still going, huh.